ets
エッツ
for
ために
it
それ
is
は
long
長さ
positive
ポジティブ
earned
稼いだ
t
t
at
で
I
私
teacher
教師
Is
は
i miss
寂しい
Our topic today is very delicate
今日の話題はとてもデリケートです
Medical Imaging in the Age of Nimi
Nimi 時代の医用画像処理
I think everyone is interested in medical imaging
医療画像には誰もが興味があると思います
between our normal lives
私たちの普段の生活の合間に
Everyone's X-rayed
全員レントゲン検査を受けました
Did you take an ultrasound, what did you take?
超音波検査を受けましたか？何を検査しましたか？
Today we have no speakers
今日はスピーカーがいません
Gu Yu Guangyan
グ・ユ・グァンヤン
He's a researcher at our nursing home
彼は私たちの老人ホームの研究員です
His research on video is many years
彼のビデオに関する研究は長年にわたる
He is going to take an X-ray image today
彼は今日レントゲン写真を撮る予定です
But his X-ray images
しかし彼のレントゲン写真は
It is higher resolution than the X-ray images we usually go to the hospital to take
私たちが普段病院で撮影するレントゲン画像よりも解像度が高いのです。
Very, very much, so it's called Naimi
とても、とても、だからナイミと呼ばれます
He'll let us know how good his resolution is then
そうすれば彼は自分の決意がどれほど素晴らしいかを私たちに教えてくれるでしょう
And it's a 3D space
そしてそれは3D空間です
Then introduce our keynote speaker today
それでは、今日の基調講演者を紹介します
Dr. Hu joined the Academia Sinica in 1992
胡博士は 1992 年に中央研究院に加わりました。
So I'm still two years old
だからまだ2歳なんだよ
He is the physics department of National Taiwan University
彼は国立台湾大学の物理学科です。
Graduated in 1982
1982年卒業
Then in Connecta and Wisconsin in the United States
その後、米国のコネタとウィスコンシンで
Ph.D.
博士号
Then he was actually doing his Ph.D.
それから彼は実際に博士号を取得していました。
synchrotron radiation
放射光
Let me introduce Taiwan by the way
ところで台湾を紹介しましょう
There is also a nice synchrotron radiation
素敵な放射光もあります
facilities in Hsinchu
新竹の施設
this is who we do the research on
私たちが調査を行っているのはこの人です
very lucky place
とても幸運な場所
Dr. Hu used the synchrotron radiation in Hsinchu
胡博士は新竹で放射光を利用した
I believe he has a lot of images today
今日はたくさんの画像があると思います
Synchrotron Radiation Facility in Hsinchu
新竹の放射光施設
Of course, in terms of synchrotron radiation
もちろん放射光に関しては
There are many facilities in the world
世の中にはたくさんの施設がありますが、
So Dr. Hu is everywhere
胡博士はどこにでもいます
Go to Europe and America
ヨーロッパやアメリカに行く
Many places are his experimental sites
多くの場所が彼の実験場です
Then he probably
それから彼はおそらく
I don't know what to say in detail
詳しくは何を言えばいいのか分からない
However, it can be seen from the title
ですが、タイトルからもわかりますが、
sometimes he tells us today
時々彼は今日私たちにこう言います
what technique does he use
彼はどんなテクニックを使っていますか
Can make an image very clear
画像を非常に鮮明にすることができます
Then he did research recently
それから彼は最近研究をしました
Also do some biological in vivo
生体内で生物学的なことも行う
It's just some images of the living body
生体のほんの一部の画像です
I don't know if he will give me today
彼が今日私にくれるかどうかわからない
his research work
彼の研究成果
It is also very prominent in this
この中でも非常に目立っています
then i talk nonsense
それから私はナンセンスを話します
So let Dr. Hu begin
それでは胡博士が始めましょう
Thank you Vice President
副社長、ありがとう
The vice president is memorized by our teacher
副社長は私たちの先生に覚えられています
so we are happy today
だから今日は幸せです
He said he was a freshman at Academia Sinica and had just arrived
彼は中央研究院の新入生で、来たばかりだと言いました。
with him in the hospital
病院にいる​​彼と一緒に
He said we are happy today
彼は私たちが今日は幸せだと言いました
I was introduced by Teacher Wang
王先生から紹介していただきました
At the same time, I also thank you very much
それと同時に、本当に感謝しています
listen at this dinner time
この夕食時に聞いてください
When I was next to this TOM
このTOMの隣にいたとき
In fact, I didn't think about it at all.
実際、まったく考えていませんでした。
I think it is
それはそうですね
Later I saw this barrier
後でこの障壁を見ました
I find again
また見つけた
so i put my 101 suit
だから私は101スーツを着ました
Where can I find hope
どこに希望を見いだすことができますか
Everyone will feel better
みんな気分も良くなりますよ
ok good
いいよ
Then what my teacher Wang said just now is
では、私の先生の王先生が今おっしゃったのは、
I probably will today
たぶん今日はそうするだろう
I will talk a little bit
少し話します
look at everyone's time
みんなの時間を見て
OK
OK
OK what I'm going to say is
OK、私が言いたいのは
Methical Imaging
メジカルイメージング
Metical Imaging This is when I was going to talk about this
メティカルイメージング これについて話そうとしたときです
I was thinking of saying I'm going to make my own stuff
自分で何か作るって言おうかと思ってた
I will say X-ray microscopy
X線顕微鏡と言いますか
or
また
But I happened to be in Europe at the time
でもその時私はたまたまヨーロッパにいました
I used to be TeeSus Advisor
我以前TeeSus Advisor
I'll just talk to him, talk about a Public Talk
ちょっと彼と話して、公開講演について話します
And he's like, oops, he's going to give this talk to the public, science talk
そして彼は、おっと、彼はこの講演を一般向けに行うつもりだ、科学の話をするつもりだ
Speaking speeches, the simplest way to say eleven is that you tell them to make money
スピーチで11を言う最も簡単な方法は、お金を稼ぐように言うことです
The second is to take care of the body according to how they do
2つ目は、自分のやり方に合わせて体のケアをすることです
I said make money, otherwise I can't teach
お金を稼げ、そうでないと教えることができないと言いました
Then I will talk about a topic related to taking care of the body.
次に、体のケアに関連したトピックについて話します。
But what we're actually doing is classifying
しかし、私たちが実際にやっていることは分類です
A lot of what we have done in recent years is about Mechanical Research
近年私たちが行ってきたことの多くは機械研究に関するものです
But how to take care of your body
しかし、自分の体をどうやってケアするか
It doesn't really matter
それはあまり関係ありません
put up business images
ビジネスの画像
I think everyone will be interested
誰もが興味を持つと思います
Another catch word
もう一つのキャッチフレーズ
This is the fancy word
これは派手な言葉です
It's Nano
ナノだよ
I think everyone has been nami
誰もがナミになったことがあると思います
It's been bombing for ten years
10年間も爆撃が続いている
So you probably want to say
だからあなたはおそらくこう言いたいのでしょう
What does Nano have to do with us?
ナノは私たちと何の関係があるのでしょうか？
I said for business
ビジネスのためって言った
So I won't talk too much about business images today
だから今日はビジネスイメージについてはあまり話さない
I don't care about MRI stuff
MRIのことは気にしない
Actually like now you are on Wikipedia
実際、今のようにあなたはウィキペディアに載っています
You can find many similar reports wherever you look.
どこを見ても同様のレポートがたくさん見つかります。
So I think my main job today
だから今日の私の主な仕事は
Just to talk about the relationship between business images and Nano
ビジネスイメージとNanoの関係についてお話します。
Business images are of course important
ビジネスイメージはもちろん重要です
I think I don't need to talk about this
これについては話す必要はないと思います
So I gave a very simple
そこで私は非常に簡単なことを言いました
The first one is an important diagnostic tool
1 つ目は重要な診断ツールです
now you go to the hospital
今、あなたは病院に行きます
especially in the last ten years
特にここ10年で
you go to the hospital
あなたは病院に行きます
we say we don't know
私たちは知らないと言います
Doctors hardly diagnose
医者はほとんど診断しない
if you have anything
何かありましたら
Remember to queue you for all the tests when he goes in
彼が入ったら、すべてのテストを受けるためにあなたを列に並べることを忘れないでください
after finishing
終わった後
in the current doctor
今の医師の中で
many young doctors
多くの若い医師
you if he didn't do these things
彼がこれらのことをしなかったら、あなたは
I'm afraid he has no way to see the evidence.
残念ながら彼には証拠を見る術がないのでしょう。
It is also said
とも言われています
Now these advances in medical imaging
医療画像技術の進歩により、
to a degree
程度に
so i'll talk a little bit later
それで、少し後で話します
S light here
ここにSライト
I know better
私はよく知っている
some of his previous history
彼の過去の歴史の一部
you will find
見つけるだろう
Actually so many of us are doing
実際、私たちの多くがやっているのは、
It's not useless on weekdays
平日はダメだよ
Today everyone can enjoy
今日はみんなで楽しめる
This better medical care
このより良い医療を
With the development of this business image
このビジネスイメージの発展に伴い、
has a great relationship
素晴らしい関係を持っています
I am at this time
私はこの時です
Let me talk about this topic first
まずはこの話題について話しましょう
This business video and unreasonable technology
このビジネスビデオと無茶苦茶な技術
what does it matter
それは何ですか
this is
これは
Let's say the first thing is to say
私たちが最初に言うことは、
Due to the development of unreasonable technology
理不尽なテクノロジーの発展により
in business images
ビジネスのイメージで
We have created new imaging principles
新しい映像原理を創造しました
this i will talk about now
これについては今から話します
we can't do it now
今はそれができない
go to particular example
特定の例に行く
But this is an important reason
しかし、これは重要な理由です
It's because you have a future that is difficult to understand technology
テクノロジーの理解が難しい未来があるから
Your previous imaging method
以前のイメージング方法
you can do it differently
違うやり方でもいいよ
you will get better
あなたは良くなるでしょう
Then of course it means
それからもちろんそれは意味します
Have better components and equipment
より良いコンポーネントと機器を持っている
So parts of these
したがって、これらの部分
I'll ask again later
後でまた質問します
Research done by myself
私自身が行った研究
i will tell you
言いますよ
you may use
使ってもいいです
I'll just say I use X-rays as an example
例として X 線を使用することにします。
what do these things mean
これらは何を意味しますか
OK
OK
Why can technology be difficult
なぜテクノロジーは難しいのか
Why does this new imaging principle
この新しいイメージング原理がなぜ実現できるのか
And it can be used to make better original parts and equipment
そして、それはより良いオリジナルの部品や機器を作るために使用できます
but one important point
しかし、重要な点が1つあります
so it's like business
だからそれはビジネスみたいなもの
The most relevant is actually
実際に最も関連性があるのは、
first lead technique or called contrast technique
ファーストリードテクニックまたはコントラストテクニックと呼ばれる
or calibration
または校正
The noun is not very uniform
名詞はあまり統一されていません
but basically
しかし基本的には
It is how you use the extra substance
余分な物質をどう使うかです
Make it this image imaging can do better
この画像イメージングをより良く行うことができるようにしてください
Well, that's why my main connection today is with Nelly.
そうですね、だから今日の私の主なつながりはネリーです。
In fact, it is on the Naili line
実はここは内里線沿いにあるんです
That is to say, for other biomedical images
つまり、他の生体画像の場合
Nai Li Xian Yin Ji
ナイ・リー・シアン・イン・ジ
Why should it be
なぜそうなる必要があるのか
we need to use nelly
ネリーを使う必要がある
Don't use the traditional way
従来の方法を使用しないでください
There must be a lot of different techniques
色々なテクニックがあるはずです
for different image formats
さまざまな画像フォーマットに対応
its important features
その重要な機能
The first one is Nelly
1人目はネリーさん
The only reason for it is that its size is important
その唯一の理由は、サイズが重要であるということです
You need to be able to reach a reasonable size
適切なサイズに到達できる必要があります
then i want everyone to know
それからみんなに知ってもらいたいです
should now be the size
今のサイズになるはずです
Everyone knows how small Naimi is
ナイミがどれほど小さいかは誰もが知っています
Nimi is 1000 times smaller than Pooh
ニミはプーさんの1000分の1です
Pooh is 1000 times smaller than Haomi
プーさんはハオミの1000分の1です
a very simple
とてもシンプルな
The size of the gills that the human body perceives
人間の体が感じるエラの大きさ
It's actually Homi
実はホミさんです
homi's words
ホミさんの言葉
Pooh
プーさん
Sorry
ごめん
hehehehe
へへへへ
Ok
Ok
so your hair is
だからあなたの髪は
Micron is Haomi or
マイクロンはハオミか
Oh ok
ああ、わかった
Hair is say 80micron
髪の毛は80ミクロンと言われています
it's pooh
プーさんです
about
左右
You can think of this Naimi
このナイミについて考えることができます
1000 times smaller than this
これより1000分の1小さい
so i wait
だから待ちます
we used to do a
私たちはかつてそれをやっていました
one
一個
Um
えーっと
very short lead is given
非常に短いリードが与えられる
Absolutely not
絶対違う
us
私たち
I am today when I was in Korea
韓国にいた頃の私は今です
At that time, South Korean President Oh Moo-hyun visited
当時、韓国の呉武鉉大統領が訪問した
the single track over there
そこのシングルトラック
That
それか
They told our cooperation team
彼らは私たちが協力したチームに言いました
he only listens to one head
彼は片方の頭の言うことしか聞かない
not three and a half
3年半じゃないよ
He said how do you tell him
彼はこう言いました、どうやって彼に伝えますか
so we talked
それで私たちは話しました
made a
を作りました
This animation is easy to say
このアニメは言うのは簡単だ
you shut it off from you
あなたはそれをあなたから遮断しました
I keep seeing this space in the middle of you
あなたの真ん中にあるこの空間をずっと見ている
how big is the gap
ギャップはどれくらいですか
we start with a
から始めます
From a human to mouse to mouse
人間からマウス、そしてマウスへ
This one organ mouse
この 1 つの臓器のマウス
How many cells are in an organ
臓器には細胞が何個あるのか
how big is the cell
細胞の大きさはどれくらいですか
Then how many cells have
では、細胞は何個あるのか
all the way down to the molecular structure
分子構造に至るまで
You know the scale of this
この規模の大きさがわかりますね
this difference in the middle
真ん中のこの違い
is very very large
とてもとても大きいです
So after looking at it like this
それでこうやって見てみたら
it just feels like
それはちょうどのように感じます
no good then what's the matter with you
ダメだよ、じゃあどうしたの？
or say for it under the microscope
または顕微鏡下でそれについて言う
You don't even realize how small it is
それがどれほど小さいかさえわかりません
The other nano
もう一つのナノ
It is the developer
開発者です
The most important thing is probably to use particles
最も重要なことはおそらくパーティクルを使用することです
Or some of these particles from oil machines
または石油機械からの粒子の一部
its composition
その構成
is that I can use many different ways
いろいろな使い方ができるということです
let this one
これをさせてください
Although a very small particle
とても小さな粒子ですが、
It's probably hundreds of atoms
おそらく数百個の原子です
or thousands of atoms
または何千もの原子
But on top there will be different composition
しかし、上部には異なる構成が存在します
And then there's the surface of it
そしてそれの表面があります
That is to say when you were so young
つまり、あなたがとても若かった頃
its surface takes up its nature
その表面はその性質を帯びています
very significant portion
非常に重要な部分
So we say its surface modification
したがって、それを表面改質と言います
or surface this
またはこれを表面化する
This presentation will cause his characteristic
このプレゼンテーションは彼の特徴を引き起こすでしょう
big difference
大きな違い
What does his nano-developer do?
彼のナノ開発者はどうですか？
Of course he can be the best first
もちろん彼が最初に一番になることもできる
Ability to Reconnect with Metabolism
代謝と再びつながる能力
means you can
できるという意味です
The second is that you can exclude
2 つ目は、除外できることです。
because you want to say
あなたが言いたいから
You are going to have an MRI
MRI検査を受ける予定です
Or when doing HRA
または HRA を行うとき
he will call you
彼はあなたに電話します
So the video camera goes in
それでビデオカメラが入ります
Then of course you hope he doesn't stay
それならもちろんあなたは彼がここに留まらないことを望みます
because it's not a good thing
それは良いことではないから
You certainly don't need to stay in the body
もちろん体内に留まる必要はありません
So his exclusion is also very important
したがって、彼の除外も非常に重要です
and now say for example
そして今、例えば言う
you want to do functional development
機能開発をしたい
is what I hope or is a manifestation of this molecule
それは私が願っていること、あるいはこの分子の現れです
what you wish you typed in
入力してほしかったこと
He will run where you want to grow
彼はあなたが成長したいところへ走ってくれるでしょう
So the professionalism of his organization is also important
したがって、彼の組織のプロフェッショナリズムも重要です
and now there is a trend
そして今トレンドがあります
that is to say I now wish
つまり私は今望んでいます
No I can now use different mods
いいえ、別の MOD を使用できるようになりました
Now everyone's every mod has been done
これで全員のMODが完成しました
The module is to image an MRI
このモジュールは MRI を画像化するためのものです
Magnetic shock photos of SPAC positron and MRI
SPAC陽電子の磁気衝撃写真とMRI
how do you put it together
どうやってまとめますか
you don't want to say
言いたくないのですか
I get a shot while I do this
これをしている間に撃たれる
You sit and wait until after a few images
数枚の画像が終わるまで座って待ちます
this person
この人
almost
ほとんど
So we hope that means
つまり、それが意味することを願っています
This is the best time
今が最高の時間です
Let this patient suffer less from this pain
この患者がこの痛みを少しでも軽減できるようにします
So it becomes an optical module imaging
つまり光学モジュールイメージングになります
It is also an important nano-developer
重要なナノ開発者でもあります
the direction of this development
この開発の方向性
In fact, I think
実際、私はそう思います
That is to say, nano developer
つまりナノデベロッパー
There is one most important Foundation
最も重要な財団が 1 つあります
this is what we think
これが私たちの考えです
this is a cartoon
これは漫画です
get it out
出してください
was supposed to explain
説明するはずだった
It means this Tumor and this Angiogenesis
それはこの腫瘍とこの血管新生を意味します
Tumor is tumor
腫瘍は腫瘍だ
This is when a tumor grows
腫瘍が大きくなる時期です
Blood vessels will have
血管は
we will now
今すぐそうします
I'm talking about a very important topic
非常に重要なテーマについて話しています
Is the senior of blood vessels
血管の先輩です
or neovascularization
または血管新生
when the tumor grows
腫瘍が大きくなったとき
this was long ago
これはずっと前のことだった
twenty or thirty years ago
二十年か三十年前
There was a doctor named Judah Fogman
ジュダ・フォグマンという名前の医師がいました
he does open up
彼は心を開いてくれます
The tumor he operated on
彼が手術した腫瘍
He found that the tumor
彼はその腫瘍を発見した
normal blood vessel density
正常な血管密度
will be much higher than normal tissue
正常組織よりもはるかに高くなります
his idea is to say
彼の考えはこう言うことだ
Because these tumors are rapidly growing
これらの腫瘍は急速に成長しているため、
he hopes
他希望
He wants to be able to have a lot of nutrients
栄養をたっぷり摂りたい
oxygen to supply him
彼に酸素を供給する
He grows up so fast
彼はとても早く成長します
So he sent out a bunch of distress calls
そこで彼はたくさんの救難信号を発信した
call these blood vessels say
これらの血管をこう呼びます
You send a tube now
今すぐチューブを送ります
oxygenate it
酸素を供給する
that's because of this
それはこのせいだ
So it will cause our nanometer today
それで、それは今日私たちのナノメートルを引き起こすでしょう
Whether this particle is used for treatment
この粒子が治療に使用されるかどうか
Or to do a very important basis for visualization
または視覚化のための非常に重要な基礎を行うため
today otherwise you can think about it
今日、そうでない場合はそれについて考えてください
Why should I use nanoparticles
なぜナノ粒子を使用する必要があるのか
molecule of this drug
この薬の分子
or molecular imaging agent
または分子イメージング剤
can do the same why
なぜ同じことができるのですか
It's this specificity these could be better
この特異性により、これらの方が優れている可能性があります
Then I think the most important difference is the nanoparticles
最も重要な違いはナノ粒子だと思います
it has this sex
それはこのセックスを持っています
That is to say, I treat my blood vessel as
つまり、私は血管を次のように扱います。
I'll keep emphasizing later
後ほど強調します
this blood vessel it
この血管は
The new blood vessels grow very broken
新しい血管は非常に壊れて成長します
its structure is not very complete
その構造はあまり完全ではありません
So it becomes you now in the middle
だから今は真ん中にいるのがあなたになる
This has particles in it
これには粒子が入っています
it will run out
それはなくなるだろう
In fact, you can be on the Internet
実際、インターネット上にいることもできます
If you go to find this called EPR
EPR と呼ばれるこれを見つけたら
Infactor
インファクター
Enhanced Permeation and Retention
強化された浸透力と保持力
give it to improve its penetration
浸透力を高めるために与えます
Follow up function
フォローアップ機能
have it this blood vessel
この血管を持っています
particle This particle will run out
パーティクル このパーティクルはなくなります
you know after running out
使い果たした後はわかります
Particles are not the same as this molecule
粒子はこの分子と同じではありません
It stays there after running out
使い果たした後もそこに残ります
It's not easy to come back smoothly
スムーズに戻るのは簡単ではない
So at this point you can
したがって、この時点でできることは、
we have many studies
私たちにはたくさんの研究があります
you can see it turn
それが変わるのがわかります
After putting this thing in
これを入れた後
its in you if you have a tumor
腫瘍があるならそれはあなたの中にあります
The blood vessels over there are very broken.
そこの血管はかなり傷んでいます。
been leaking
漏れている
like you want to turn on a faucet
蛇口をひねりたいように
There's a leak all over you
あなたの全身から漏れがあります
it just keeps leaking
漏れ続けるだけです
There will be a lot of water at the end
最後には水がたくさん出てきます
So this can be done
それでこれができるのです
This tumor-resistant drug
この抗がん剤は
or tumor-resistant adenitis
または腫瘍抵抗性腺炎
today we are very simple
今日の私たちはとてもシンプルです
it means i want to see the stream
それはストリームを見たいという意味です
You said I typed something in
あなたは私が何かを入力したと言った
it will stay there
そこに留まるだろう
I just need to detect in this body
この体で検出するだけでいい
where is there a lot of this
これがたくさんあるのはどこですか
then i'm one
それなら私もその一人です
Can hear clearly with microphone
マイクではっきりと聞こえる
Huh? There is a microphone
あれ？マイクあるよ
should be open
開いているはずです
right
右
OK
OK
OK too high
まあ高すぎます
OK good
いいよ
That
それか
OK so this part is
OK、この部分は
with this nano
このナノで
That is to say, the medicine behind nano
つまり、ナノの背後にある薬
In fact, there is a major relationship
実は大きな関係があるのです
that is
あれは
The tumor angiogenesis
腫瘍の血管新生
would cause this to be different from normal this
これは通常とは異なる原因になります
where the organization is different
組織が違うところ
so that you can have this specificity
この特異性を実現できるように
And this is a
そして、これは
What we replace is to say
私たちが置き換えるのは、次のようなことです
you can see that is to say
つまりそれはわかります
I had a small one here
ここに小さいのあったよ
cancer cells clump together
がん細胞が凝集する
when it starts to turn into a tumor
腫瘍になり始めると
it will flow from this artery
この動脈から流れてくるだろう
or venous
または静脈性
let them grow these blood vessels
この血管を成長させてください
provide it with nutrients
栄養を与えてあげる
OK
OK
That's the same as this example
この例と同じです
then we are talking now
それなら今話しています
In this common way of medical imaging
この一般的な医用画像処理方法では、
There are a few that I can't introduce one by one
一つ一つ紹介しきれないものもありますが、
but basically they
しかし基本的に彼らは
In fact, I just said that if you classify
実際、分類すると、先ほど言いました。
to this
これに
The principles are very similar
原理は非常に似ています
Just my first one I ever need to have a thing to go
行く必要があるのは初めてのことだけ
to where you want to see
見たいところへ
For example, in the way of this single-gloss paper
たとえば、この単光沢紙の場合
This is using a
これは、
You put a substance of this radiation
あなたはこの放射線の物質を入れます
hit into the body
体に当たる
This radioactive material emits this
この放射性物質はこれを放出します
This GAMRAID
このガムレイド
at this time you outside
今度はあなたは外にいる
If there is a GAMRAID camera
GAMRAID カメラがある場合
you can take
どうぞ
Tell me if this camera can take pictures
このカメラで写真が撮れるか教えてください
where did it come from
それはどこから来たの
Then it might have some
そうすれば、いくつかあるかもしれません
bring some products
いくつかの製品を持ってくる
Or it has a special calibration function
または特別なキャリブレーション機能があります
then you can see where it's staying
そうすればそれがどこに残っているかがわかります
or how it will be brought
またはそれがどのようにもたらされるか
You will achieve the role of this visualization
この視覚化の効果が得られます
That or the positron way
それか陽電子の道か
The positron method means using a positron
陽電子法とは、陽電子を利用することをいいます。
It will be I-Mate
アイメイトになります
will be wiped out
一掃されるだろう
It's this Zhengzi and this
これは鄭子とこれです
are positively charged electrons
正に帯電した電子です
Is a
です
if it collides with electrons
電子と衝突すると
It will generate about 500KV or so of this
約500KV程度の電圧が発生します
This GAMRAID
このガムレイド
it's in there
そこにあります
because it is gone after
後はなくなったから
Just release this GAMRAID
この GAMRAID をリリースするだけです
GAMRAID it will generate
GAMRAID が生成されます
I've been walking in the lazy direction since I was a kid
子供の頃から怠惰な方向に歩いてきた
So I grab these two from the entity
そこで、エンティティからこれら 2 つを取得します
The words of this Gamma Ray of this Gamma Ray
このガンマ線の言葉 このガンマ線の言葉
I just draw a line
ただ線を引くだけです
I know where your stuff comes from
あなたのものがどこから来たのか知っています
That's the way to know where your stuff is
それが自分の持ち物がどこにあるかを知る方法です
produced
生産された
Those things are not human
それらは人間ではありません
It's something you typed in
それはあなたが入力したものです
So when you go to the hospital
それで病院に行ったら
If the doctor tells you this time
今度はお医者さんに言われたら
You'd better ask if it's necessary
必要かどうか聞いたほうがいいよ
Because doctors don't want to deal with these things themselves.
なぜなら、医師は自らこれらのことに対処したくないからです。
It's all radioactive
全部放射性物質だよ
Although its half-life may be short
半減期は短いかもしれないが
like two days or three days
2日か3日くらい
so i tried this
それで私はこれを試しました
Every medical image
あらゆる医療画像
it has its very important role
それは非常に重要な役割を持っています
But every side effect it must fall below it
しかし、あらゆる副作用はそれを下回らなければなりません
So I guess it means
だからそれは意味があると思います
most doctors he is not too
ほとんどの医者は彼もそうではない
i'm not saying there's something wrong with the doctor
医者に何か問題があると言っているわけではない
Rather, the system now
むしろ今のシステムは
like my father
私の父のように
He wants everyone their age
彼はみんなに同じ年齢を望んでいる
He likes to look like Shopping
彼はショッピングしているように見えるのが好きです
he is in a different hospital
彼は別の病院にいます
Come to the hospital here to have a look
ここの病院に来て見てください
he felt unhappy he went to the inner courtyard
彼は不幸を感じて中庭へ行った
But if you go to this one today
でも今日ここに行くなら
He asks you to be a CT
彼はあなたにCTになってほしいと頼んだ
That family asked you to be a CT again
その家族はあなたにもう一度CTを依頼しました
this one in Taiwan
これは台湾にある
Not registered on your health insurance card
健康保険証に登録されていない
So you end up finding yourself doing it multiple times a year
結局、年に何回も同じことをすることになる
No matter how safe he says it is
どんなに安全だと彼が言ったとしても
You still end up with radiation damage
それでも放射線障害を受けることになる
then we used to have a
それから私たちはかつて持っていました
Academician of the American Academy of Sciences told us
アメリカ科学アカデミーの学者が私たちに語った。
That is to say, this kind of sixty or seventy-year-old
つまり、このような60歳か70歳の人は、
He said that we all check another Mutation
彼は、私たちは皆、別の突然変異をチェックしていると言いました
will get cancer
癌になるだろう
One Mutation around
周囲に1つの突然変異
So it has better be careful
だから気を付けたほうがいいよ
Then let me say this, for example,
じゃあ、例えばこう言わせてください。
to me just finished
終わったばかりの私にとって
here for example
たとえばここで
Ultrasound this is now
超音波これは今です
Recognized as the least damaged
被害が最も少ないと認められる
So many people now think that ultrasound
現在、非常に多くの人が超音波だと考えています。
Said that the ultrasound will be better and better
超音波はますます良くなるだろうと言いました
He will probably replace most of this medical imaging
彼はおそらくこの医療画像の大部分を置き換えることになるでしょう
That benevolent care is also a very Pobby
その慈悲深い心遣いもとてもポビーですね
But benevolent care has one of the biggest problems
しかし、慈善的なケアには最大の問題の 1 つがあります
For example like my dad he has this Pace Maker
たとえば、私の父と同じように、彼はこのペースメーカーを持っています
have this starter
このスターターを持っています
he can't do it
彼にはそれができない
Then X-ray does not have this problem
そうすればX線にはこの問題はありません
but x-ray wait a minute i'll talk
でもレントゲン、ちょっと待ってください、話します
it's his pity
それは彼の残念さだ
He will also have this radioactive
彼もこの放射性物質を持っているでしょう
The problem of radiation damage
放射線障害の問題
Then you can this picture is us
それなら、この写真が私たちです
I copy down
コピーダウンします
that is to say basically
つまり基本的に
every image of you
あなたのあらゆるイメージ
His Limit degree
彼の限界度
with his resolution
彼の決意とともに
it's all
それがすべてです
so you might just say
だからあなたはただこう言うかもしれません
what do i need to see
何を見るべきですか
What kind of video mode do I want to use
どのような画像モードを使用すればよいですか
that's very important
それはとても重要です
I have a few pictures here
ここにいくつかの写真があります
I won't talk about it one by one
いちいち話さないよ
That's basically this
それは基本的にこれです
you went to the hospital
あなたは病院に行きました
when you put it in
それを入れるとき
you probably know this
あなたはおそらくこれを知っています
For example, he is now afraid that you
たとえば、彼は今あなたがいることを恐れています。
If you don't ask you can't figure it out
聞かないと分からないよ
is he masago or spac
彼はマサゴですか、それともスパクですか
or mri
またはmri
Anyway, it's the same as going into a hole
どうせ穴に入るのと同じだ
and tell you to sit over there
そしてそこに座るように言います
kind of good
なんだか良い
and put you in later
そして後であなたを入れてください
Doctors just ran away
医師たちはただ逃げた
like positron emission because it's a radioactive substance
放射性物質なので陽電子放出のようなもの
So it needs an accelerator to be able to produce this kind of isodigit
したがって、この種のアイソデジットを生成できるようにするにはアクセラレータが必要です
Ultrasound now also has a lot of progress
超音波も今では大きく進歩しています
For example, basically it talks about the three-dimensional space
たとえば、基本的には 3 次元空間について話します。
They even talk about ultrasound in the fourth dimension
彼らは四次元の超音波についてさえ話します
Then I don't care about it
それなら気にしないよ
Basically it means that it gives you the same thing that you can say it
基本的に、それはあなたが言うことができるのと同じことをあなたに与えることを意味します
In the past, for example, we said that you want to see this pregnant woman
たとえば、以前、この妊婦に会いたいと言ったことがあります。
You have to see her child, she is in the clouds, you will see a look
あなたは彼女の子供に会わなければなりません、彼女は雲の中にいます、あなたはその姿を見るでしょう
It is possible now, that is to say, it can be viewed from three angles at the same time
同時に3つの角度から見ることができるようになりました
These are big improvements
これらは大きな改善です
There is one for ultrasound, and I borrowed this from a research friend of ours.
超音波用のものがあるのですが、これは研究仲間から借りました。
That is, one of them has something to do with ultrasound and treatment
つまり、そのうちの1つは超音波と治療に関係しています。
It's inside the micro-explosion they use ultrasonic waves
超音波を使用した微小爆発の内部です
with whether it's the gene, the gene they need to deliver or the drug
それが遺伝子なのか、送達する必要がある遺伝子なのか、それとも薬物なのか
and ultrasonically blast this micro cannon to shatter it
このマイクロキャノンを超音波で爆破して粉砕します
This is a normal process
これは通常のプロセスです
But because of this shattering
しかし、この粉砕のせいで
Sometimes the first of many people is to say
時々、多くの人が最初にこう言うことがあります。
It can actually be used to treat cancer
実はガンの治療にも使えるんです
That is because when you sleep
それはあなたが寝るときだからです
this his this shockwave
これはこの衝撃波です
When he was broken
彼が壊れたとき
this power is great
この力は素晴らしいです
because I remember that in
それを覚えているから
when they said the earliest
彼らが一番早いと言ったとき
at the time of World War I
第一次世界大戦時
The propeller of the ship they found
彼らが見つけた船のプロペラ
often breaks
頻繁に壊れる
easily damaged
傷つきやすい
It took him a long time to know that
彼がそれを知るのに長い時間がかかった
So it was your propeller that went out
プロペラが故障したことが判明しました
You have that blister when the blister pops
水ぶくれがはじけると水ぶくれができます
His strength is very great
彼の強さはとても大きいです
You can hit this movement on this metal
この金属でこの動きを打つことができます
So they then said
それで彼らはこう言いました
I will improve
改善していきます
So don't create so many bubbles
だからあまり泡を作らないでください
So this force of this bubble
この泡の力は
That is to say, when we were actually making videos in the past,
というのは、昔、実際に動画を作っていたときに、
hope to catch him
彼を捕まえることを願っています
the first one he was very fast
最初の試合では彼はとても速かった
It's him you and us become one ex
それは彼です あなたと私たちは一つの元になります
Saw this a while ago
これを少し前に見た
Suddenly he disappeared
突然彼は姿を消しました
he exploded
彼は爆発した
At this time he produced this position
この時点で彼はこのポジションを生み出しました
they are called shockwave
それらは衝撃波と呼ばれます
just like this is not normal
これは普通ではないのと同じように
his this will not
彼のこれはそうではありません
Its spread these are not the same
その広がりは同じではありません
So it will be very lethal to this cell
したがって、それはこの細胞にとって非常に致死的になります
especially small ones
特に小さいものは
The other way is after I put the genuine goods
じゃあもう一つは純正品を入れた後です
words near it
その近くの言葉
It is very possible that what I have on the inside
私が内側に持っているものは可能性が非常に高いです
Enter this cell to achieve the purpose you want
目的を達成するにはこのセルに入力してください
Then this is ultrasound, which is related to this
それから、これは超音波です。これはこれに関連しています。
useful place
便利な場所
You can see that the MRI is basically the same.
MRIも基本的には同じであることがわかります。
Then people here he wants
それから彼がここに欲しい人たち
For example, when you want to be the head
たとえば、頭になりたいとき
He's gonna fix your head
彼はあなたの頭を正してくれるでしょう
Then this you can see images like this
すると、このような画像が表示されます
That is to say, the biggest advantage of MRI is that
つまり、MRIの最大の利点は、
It is actually beneficial to soft tissue
実際に軟部組織に有益です
Because it is mainly to image this clear
これを鮮明にイメージすることが主なので
As long as you want it to be where there is water, it can
水のある場所に置きたいと思う限り、それは可能です
Then of course it has many other variations
もちろん他にもたくさんのバリエーションがあります
There are functional MRI
機能性MRIもある
diffuse MRI
びまん性MRI
It's anyway or you mix this developer differently
とにかく、この開発者を別の方法で組み合わせます
Doing it can do great imaging
そうすることで優れたイメージングが可能になります
that MRI and it's not very accessible
MRIはあまりアクセスしにくい
It's just that the damage to human nature is not high.
ただ、人体への被害はそれほど高くありません。
Of course sometimes you still have to apply developer
もちろん、開発者を適用する必要がある場合もあります
the developer
この開発者
Everyone says that this is passed by the food hygiene in the United States.
これはアメリカの食品衛生で合格していると誰もが言います。
but you play too much
でもあなたは遊びすぎます
you will feel uncomfortable
あなたは不快に感じるでしょう
OK
OK
So this is an MRI
ということで、これはMRIです
So now I use very very Popular
だから今私は非常に人気のあるものを使用しています
But there is a problem with MRI relative
しかし、MRI関連には問題があります
it's because it's still expensive
それはまだ高価だからです
So if you go, if the health insurance does not pay
それで、行った場合、健康保険が支払われない場合は、
For example, now someone is
たとえば、今、誰かが
Just want to do this with MRI
これをMRIでやりたいだけ
breast design
胸のデザイン
Then if you do X-ray in general, it may be covered by health insurance
そうすると、一般的なレントゲン検査をすれば健康保険が適用される可能性があります。
But if the MRI is not paid for
ただし、MRIの費用が支払われない場合は、
It might cost you 20,000 yuan to do it once
1回やるのに2万円くらいかかるかも
Of course there are considerable benefits
もちろんメリットも大きい
But even that probably isn't
しかし、それさえおそらくそうではありません
This image that will become the front line
最前線となるこのイメージ
Then I just said that this is an example I gave
それから、これは私が挙げた例だと言いました
because i think of nanodiamonds
ナノダイヤモンドのことを考えているから
Our Zhonglian Rag has a very strong this
私たちの中連ラグはこれが非常に強いです
I really have this team that has done a good job
本当に良い仕事をしたチームがいる
They're making nanodiamonds
彼らはナノダイヤモンドを作っている
nano diamonds you put some of these on
ナノダイヤモンド、あなたはこれをいくつか付けます
These materials you want to attach
添付したい資料はこちら
it has some faith in itself
それ自体にある程度の信念がある
It can also be used as a tool for confidence imaging
信頼性イメージングのツールとしても使用できます
I'm going to find this
これを見つけてみます
I originally wanted to talk to this licensed radiography and Naimi
もともと私はこの認可されたレントゲン撮影とナイミと話したかったのです
what is the relationship
関係は何ですか
Except for this developing machine
この開発機を除いて
Later I found out that they said
後で彼らが言っていたことを知りました
You can do Naimi licensed radiography
ナイミ認可のレントゲン撮影が可能です
I went to see this paper
この新聞を見に行きました
Said it can do 70 resistance meters
70メートルの抵抗ができるとのこと
I think that's a big deal
それは大変なことだと思う
after that
その後
Only then did he realize that they were not
そのとき初めて、彼はそれらがそうではないことに気づきました
They're here to look at the surface
彼らは表面を見るためにここにいます
It is increased or decreased by this
これで増えたり減ったり
with AFM
用AFM的方式
For example, this Tommy Force Microscope
たとえば、このトミーフォース顕微鏡
With a very shoulder this scene
とても肩を組んでこのシーン
and then be able to swipe across the surface
表面をスワイプできるようになります
because it is very local
とてもローカルなので
Give it a very strong field
非常に強力なフィールドを与えてください
or gradient
またはグラデーション
it can cause MRI-like
MRIのような症状を引き起こす可能性があります
This has the same effect as this licensed radiography
これは、この許可された放射線撮影と同じ効果があります。
So this has nothing to do with medical imaging
したがって、これは医療画像とは何の関係もありません
probably nothing
おそらく何もない
even images of living things
生き物の画像も
I'm afraid it will be difficult
難しいと思います
then i won't talk
それなら話さないよ
then ourselves
それから私たち自身
team of friends cooperating inside
内部で協力する友人のチーム
We have a Spec with MicroCT and PAC at the National Institutes of Health
国立衛生研究所にはMicroCTとPACの仕様があります
these three put together
この3つを合わせたもの
it's my machine
それは私のマシンです
just one hole
穴が一つだけ
you don't do three holes
3つの穴はやらない
a round this
これを一周
then just be a mouse
それならただのネズミになってください
its a small hole
それは小さな穴です
After securing the mice and sending them over
ネズミを確保して送り届けたら
You can do Spec at the same time
スペックも同時に行うことができます
Then also get this PAC
それから、この PAC も入手してください
Also get CT
CTも取得
we are here
私たちはここにいる
I'm learning from this example now
私は今この例から学んでいます
This team basically hopes to develop different
このチームは基本的に異なるものを開発したいと考えています
radio isotope
ラジオアイソトープ
The radio isotope is already known to be very fixed
放射性同位体は非常に固定されていることがすでに知られています
what are they doing
彼らは何をしていますか
it just said
それはただ言った
please get different antibodies
いろいろな抗体を入手してください
or a different molecule
または別の分子
so that it can selectively go where
選択的にどこにでも行けるように
different places
別の場所
Then use the line that measures against it this way
次に、このようにそれを対策する線を使用します
to know where it is
それがどこにあるかを知るために
I won't go into detail about this part
この部分については詳しく説明しません
Because this is probably a few pictures I can show
これはおそらく私が見せられる数枚の写真なので
It's a mouse
ネズミです
you can see what i typed in
私が入力した内容がわかります
you just know
あなたはただ知っています
That is to say, this may be in the heart
つまりこれは心の中にあるのかもしれない
you just know it's gonna come here
それがここに来ることはわかっているはずだ
This is this image of this
この画像のこれです
clearer like this
このようにより明確に
You can see like this SPECT image
こんなSPECT画像が見られます
it looks at this radial isotope
この放射状同位体を観察します
this is radioactive
これは放射性です
After this is added, it has a special function
これを追加すると、特別な機能が追加されます
You can see something like this actually outside of this
実際にこの外にこのようなものを見ることができます
Neither is SPECT
スペクトでもない
These skeletons outside are actually made of X-ray
屋外にあるこれらの骸骨は実際には X 線で作られています
Its SPECT index will tell you
そのSPECTインデックスが教えてくれます
Where are these things you will light up
あなたが照らすこれらのものはどこにありますか
This skeleton is just to let you know
このスケルトンは単にお知らせするためのものです
where do you take the mouse
マウスをどこに持っていきますか
These are probably images of SPECT
おそらくSPECTの画像です
OK, I will finish my general introduction
さて、全体的な紹介を終わります
For File
ファイル用
It's like a doctor's hospital
医者の病院みたいです
Now I'm going to talk about what I did
これから私が何をしたか話します
Of course when you do it yourself
もちろん自分でやる場合も
I must say that the previous ones are not good.
以前のものは良くないと言わざるを得ません。
right? I did it myself.
そうだね?自分でやったんだ。
Otherwise why would I do it right?
そうでなければ、なぜそれを正しく行うのでしょうか？
good first thing
まず最初に良いこと
I'm going to say now that I do X-ray
今からレントゲン検査をすると言ってみます
Because the vice president just said
さっき副社長が言ってたから
I've been doing it since I started
始めた頃からずっとやってる
This is where the research begins
ここから研究が始まります
I'm in synchrotron radiation
私は放射光の中にいる
So that's why I got synchrotron radiation
だから放射光を手に入れたんだ
I can't do anything else
他に何もできない
So that synchrotron radiation
つまり、放射光は
is that it produces a lot of light
それはたくさんの光を生み出すということです
We just can't do every light
すべてのライトを実現することはできません
we did x-ray
私たちはX線検査をしました
X-ray it's just saying
X線、それはただ言っているだけです
with these other
これらの他のものと
i don't mean it per se
それ自体は意味がありません
with these other blue pens
他の青いペンを使って
what good is it
それは何ですか
The first is when it is used for imaging
1つ目は画像処理に使用する場合です。
it has one of the biggest benefits
それは最大の利点の1つです
That is, the range of things that can be seen is very large.
つまり、見える範囲が非常に広いということです。
You see we can get from animals
動物から得ることができるのがわかりますか
that of course you all know
それはもちろん皆さんご存知です
man is an animal
人間は動物です
So there is no problem for you to take X-ray photos
レントゲン写真を撮っても問題ありません
That family has this X-ray that can take pictures
あの家族は写真が撮れるレントゲンを持っています
according to this elephant
この象によると
and then there is
そしてそこにあります
can take more
もっと取れる
The most important benefit is its high penetration
最大のメリットは浸透力の高さです
I'll start over later
後で最初からやり直します
Another benefit is that its wavelength
もう一つの利点は、その波長です。
For example, when we use an Astron
たとえば、アストロンを使用する場合、
It's one tenth of a rice
お米の10分の1です
or shorter at this wavelength
この波長以下では
So the advantage of its short wavelength
つまり、波長が短いことの利点は、
It's kind of like when it's going this way
こうなってくるとこんな感じです
straight line particles
直線粒子
it doesn't have much volatility
ボラティリティはあまりありません
At this time, it is your wave
このとき、それはあなたの波です
when your waves are so short
あなたの波がとても短いとき
when you want to make it like
みたいにしたいとき
For example, I make an optical microscope
たとえば、私は光学顕微鏡を作ります。
I want to make a Lens
レンズを作りたい
It's usually if you guys remember this high school physics
これは高校の物理を覚えていればよくあることですが、
How is its resolution defined?
その解像度はどのように定義されていますか?
Its resolution depends on your wavelength
解像度は波長によって異なります
So something as simple as
したがって、次のような単純なこと
You're like this one in the semiconductor field
半導体分野ではこんな感じです
we felt a few years ago
私たちは数年前に感じた
Aya they make this device
アヤはこの装置を作っています
Make it 0.25 micron and it will be the end
0.25ミクロンにして終わりです
because they're doing it with visible light
可視光でやっているから
Do Ligography
リゴグラフィーを行う
do this lithography
このリソグラフィーを行う
then your light is
そうすればあなたの光は
is 500nm
500nmです
you have to do what you say
あなたは言うことをやらなければなりません
How do you make this smaller? It's about half
これをどうやって小さくするのですか?半分くらいです
Its wavelength is the end
その波長は終わりだ
Then we think they can't do this anymore
その場合、彼らはもうこれを行うことができないと思います
But A anyway they invented a lot of weird ways
でも、とにかく彼らはたくさんの奇妙な方法を発明しました
A just keep going
ただ前に進み続けるだけ
Since then, people have been talking about
それ以来、人々は次のように話しています。
We should do this moment with S light
この瞬間をSライトでやるべきだ
this lithography
このリトグラフ
Because the wavelength of S light is so short
S光は波長が短いので
away from it this
それから離れてこれ
will be limited by its wavelength
波長によって制限される
Our name is Defreshing Limit
私たちの名前は Defreshing Limit
far away
遠く
Well, this is of course another benefit for us.
もちろん、これは私たちにとってもう 1 つの利点です。
That is to say, we dont care about doing X-ray today
つまり、今日はX線検査をする必要はありません
What kind of Resolution
どのような解像度ですか
far from this
ここから遠く離れた
So we are not limited by this physical basis
したがって、私たちはこの物理的基盤に制限されません
limited to
に限定される
Then another X-ray
それからまたレントゲン
Except when first invented
最初に発明されたときを除いて
It is not used to make images
画像作成には使用しません
soon everyone will find out
すぐにみんなが気づくだろう
Although it is what I just said
今言った事なんですけども
Although it has few fluctuating properties
変動特性は少ないものの、
in imaging it looks like
画像では次のように見えます
But actually it still has
しかし実際にはまだ残っている
it's still a wave
まだ波です
Then you can have backshot and can eat
そうすればバックショットも食べられるし
These are all available
これらはすべて利用可能です
It is X-ray deflection
X線偏向です
It is the diffraction of X1
X1の回折です
a person who makes materials
素材を作る人
almost everyone
ほとんどの人
like our vice president
私たちの副大統領のように
He's an expert at doing this X-ray scattering
彼はこの X 線散乱の専門家です
He did it from a very young age
彼は幼い頃からそれをやっていました
That fan shot too
あのファンショットも
In fact, it is the same X-ray physics
実際、それは同じ X 線物理学です
That part is actually
その部分は実は
Materials Science is also provided
材料科学も提供されます
Physics is also good
物理も得意です
a very large
一個非常大的
This is a very useful tool
これはとても便利なツールです
that recently someone was saying
最近誰かが言っていたこと
We actually diffract
実際に回折します
Let's say I have a crystal
私がクリスタルを持っているとしましょう
I have a material
資料があるよ
i want to know what it is made of
何でできているのか知りたいです
the easiest way
最も簡単な方法
In fact, it is to do an X-ray diffraction
実際には、X線回折を行うことです
Then because you know
それなら、あなたは知っているから
you know the arrangement of its atoms
あなたはその原子の配置を知っています
how to line up
並ぶ方法
Then what is its crystal structure
ではその結晶構造はどうなっているのでしょうか
You can get very complete information
非常に充実した情報を得ることができます
But if your structure
しかし、あなたの構造が
not to say that there is no periodicity
周期性がないとは言えません
For example, if you don't tie the crystal award
例えばクリスタル賞を結ばなかった場合
just me
私だけ
A single molecule or a bunch is this
単一の分子または束はこれです
called morphous
有形と呼ばれる
just out of order
ただ調子が悪いだけ
Then you will be in X-ray like this
そうするとレントゲンではこんな感じになります
Because X-ray is relying on it
X線が頼りなので
After each thing is arranged periodically
それぞれのことを定期的に整理してから
it produces this constructive interference
それはこの建設的な干渉を生み出します
You will only be able to detect it later
後でのみ検出できるようになります
you know when it comes out
それがいつ出てくるか知っていますか
Scattering is sure to scatter
散るは必ず散る
just be with me light hits anything and it scatter
ただ一緒にいてください 光は何かに当たって散乱します
But it won't have a strong
でも強いことはないでしょう
this reflected this
これはこれを反映しました
Or let you detect
または、検出できるようになります
So someone recently said
それで最近誰かが言いました
In fact, if my diffraction is strong enough
実際、私の回折が十分に強ければ
I can still do it like
まだこんな感じに作れますよ
Because no matter what
だって何があっても
scattered things
散らばったもの
I can reassemble it back to its original essence
元の本質に戻して組み立てることができます
I'll wait a while for this
時間があればこれも待ってます
i might talk
話すかもしれない
but this is a bit
でもこれはちょっと
Because it's still a long way from being an actual hero
本当のヒーローにはまだまだ遠いから
And then of course it's X-ray it has to do
そしてもちろんX線検査も必要です
For example, your X-ray
たとえば、レントゲン写真
You can also do energy spectrum analysis on this X-ray
この X 線でエネルギー スペクトル分析を行うこともできます。
For example, the absorption of X-rays
例えば、X線の吸収
It is directly related to each material
それぞれの素材と直接関係しています
each element
それぞれの要素
its absorbing properties
その吸収特性
are not the same
都不太一樣
It follows your atomic number
それはあなたの原子番号に続きます
then when you absorb
それからあなたが吸収するとき
The chemical state of each element
各元素の化学状態
it's the state of this chemical piece
それがこの化学物質の状態です
Differently, its absorption will also
それとは異なり、その吸収はまた、
The absorption of wind will also change slightly
風の吸収も若干変わります
So you do it this absorption supplement
だからあなたはこの吸収サプリメントをやります
or launch supplement
またはサプリメントを発売する
You can get a lot of this material about it
それに関する資料をたくさん入手できます
Or this analysis of this chemical state
あるいはこの化学状態の分析
Then we actually put it behind this time.
それから、今回は実際にそれを後ろに置きました。
Not that it's as important as this thing
これほど重要というわけではない
It's rather new
むしろ新しいですね
Then it now means that in addition to the previous
すると、以前のものに加えて、
The absorbable imaging we just talked about
先ほど話した吸収性イメージング
Now there is one more new imaging mechanism for this
このための新しいイメージング メカニズムがもう 1 つあります。
I'll take a moment to introduce this then wait a minute
ちょっと時間をかけてご紹介しますので、少々お待ちください
Of course X-ray is of course
レントゲンはもちろん
I think that's when X-ray was discovered in the first place
X線が最初に発見されたのはその時だったと思います
Just now the vice president was still talking about
たった今、副大統領がまだ話していました
he watched some old this
彼は古いこれを見ました
example
例
That's when X-rays were first discovered
X線が初めて発見されたのはこの時だった
everyone is crazy
誰もが狂っている
And then it's basically like having this vending machine
そして基本的にはこの自動販売機があるようなものです
you can drop a dollar
1ドル落としてもいいよ
It will make an S-Fone for you
S-Foneを作ってくれます
You can see something like this when Google in 2010
2010 年に Google で検索すると、次のようなものが表示されます。
That time was 115 years
その時は115年でした
Commemoration of Mun Kwon's discovery of X-rays
ムングォン氏のX線発見記念
The earliest this is the first X-ray image
最も古いものは、最初の X 線画像です
This image is said to be his wife's hand
この画像は妻の手と言われています
So I say he was pretty smart back then
それで私は、彼は当時かなり賢かったと言いました
I probably know what I'm doing
私はおそらく自分が何をしているのか知っています
It's his wife
彼の妻です
OK
OK
so
それで
so from then on
だからそれ以来
The biggest advantage of X is why he is called X
X の最大の利点は、彼が X と呼ばれる理由です
is that he is a mystery
彼は謎だということ
he is a very mysterious
彼はとても神秘的です
He shows you things you couldn't see before
彼はあなたに今まで見えなかったものを見せてくれる
like me
私のような
I mean, I'm going to watch a movie on the plane
飛行機の中で映画を見るつもりだ
I think this is exactly what we're doing
これはまさに私たちがやっていることだと思います
That is to say, this is in this movie
つまり、これがこの映画の中にあるのです
He said this is the one from the life magazine
彼は、これはライフ誌からのものだと言いました
same name
同じ名前
To him is to see behind the walls
彼にとって壁の向こうを見ることは
It is exactly what we X can do
それはまさに私たちXにできることです
How about seeing from behind the wall you can see
見える壁の向こう側から眺めてみてはいかがでしょうか
Like this is the X-ray image
レントゲン画像はこんな感じ
They scan the whole container
彼らはコンテナ全体をスキャンします
You can actually see X-ray
実際にレントゲンを見ることができます
So of course you can see behind this wall
もちろんこの壁の後ろも見えます
Look at this is also the most brief
見てください、これも最も簡潔です
like this you can see he can scan the whole
このようにして、彼が全体をスキャンできることがわかります
Connected to the engine of his car
彼の車のエンジンに接続されている
can see clearly
はっきりと見える
Let's say this is an example
これが例だとしましょう
They saw a container inside
彼らは中にコンテナがあるのを見ました
There are dozens of hundreds of illegal immigrants
何十、何百人もの不法移民がいる
One more border from Mexico to the United States
メキシコから米国への国境がまた一つ増えた
So this device of the Agrin sun
つまり、このアグリン太陽の装置は
The way he scans is actually like this
実際のスキャン方法はこんな感じ
He said one is fixed
彼は一つは直ったと言った
a big block
大きなブロック
In addition, he is still active
さらに、彼は今でも活動しています
like this, for example, this machine
このように、たとえばこのマシン
He put it on this truck
彼はそれをこのトラックに乗せた
He can go to the container terminal
彼はコンテナターミナルに行くことができます
they all sweep it over
彼らは皆それを一掃する
He knew what was in there
彼はそこに何があるか知っていた
like this is actually a good
これは実際に良いことです
This technology transfer
今回の技術移転は
This topic is all the big scanners in the mainland
このトピックは本土のすべての大型スキャナーです
They are all calculated by Tsinghua University in Beijing.
これらはすべて北京の清華大学によって計算されています。
So Beijing Tsinghua University relies on this year alone
したがって、北京清華大学は今年だけを頼りにしています
I heard that there can be four to five billion RAM
RAM は 40 ～ 50 億個あると聞きました
Means this Bloyote is back
つまり、このブロオテが戻ってきたということです
That's generally speaking
それは一般的に言えば
I said you can see
見えると言いました
That's why we love X-ray
それが私たちがX線を愛する理由です
Just say you see this is not our own invention
これは私たち自身の発明ではないことがわかりましたと言ってください
It was in the United States
それはアメリカでした
I can sell you a pair of glasses
メガネをお売りいただけます
It can be like having an X-ray edition
X線検査のようなものかもしれません
Everyone, look how happy he is
みんな、彼がどれほど幸せか見てください
and a dollar
そしてドル
OK
OK
of course it's fake
もちろん偽物です
But that means you can know that everyone is right
でもそれは、誰もが正しいと知ることができることを意味します
this period in childhood
幼少期のこの時期
We've always wanted superhuman strength
私たちはいつも超人的な力を望んでいた
you can see through this wall
この壁を通して見ることができます
This is X-ray
これはX線です
One of the most interesting things
最も興味深いことの 1 つは
like this
このような
This is what I found on Google
Googleで見つけたのがこれです
funny cartoon
面白い漫画
Then for example like this
すると、例えばこんな感じで
Also we can see all the things
また、すべてのものを見ることができます
OK, this is actually made by the same company
はい、これは実は同じ会社が作ったものです
And just talking to the vice president
そして副社長と話しているところです
Everyone uses it for everything
誰もが何にでも使います
Back then someone was shooting X-ray movies
その頃誰かがX線映画を撮影していた
Not an X-ray movie
X線映画ではありません
It's an X-ray movie, that means everyone go
これは X 線映画です、つまり全員が行くことを意味します
just watch it move
ただ動くのを見てください
Then you can watch them with X-ray
その後、X線で観察することができます
Let's see if your shoes fit
あなたの靴が合うかどうか見てみましょう
I hope it still has this foot after two years
2年後もこの足が残ってればいいのですが
Then there are, for example
それから、例えば、
I don't know if you have this
これを持っているかどうかはわかりません
download the app for this phone
この携帯電話用のアプリをダウンロード
Just say that after you take a photo
写真撮ったらそう言ってください
after photo
写真アップ後
you look like
あなたは次のように見えます
although it's fake
偽物ですが
it's not real
それは本当ではない
then like these
それからこれらのように
Of course there are serious applications
もちろん本格的な用途もあります
Like say this is
これはこうだと言うように
X-ray is a very important application
X線は非常に重要な用途です
I mean I want to see these
つまり、これらが見たいのです
Whether my semiconductor manufacturing process is wind
私の半導体製造プロセスは風力かどうか
After these are done
これらが完了したら
don't need to open
開く必要はありません
so at this time
だからこの時点では
this is what we did
これが私たちがやったことです
because we are limited by our
なぜなら、私たちは自分たちのものによって制限されているからです
This is what we call Fuel of View
これを私たちは「燃料」と呼んでいます。
First we are the size of the window
まずウィンドウのサイズです
So we for example say
したがって、たとえば次のように言います
This SD memory card we have to take photos all the time
常にSDメモリーカードの写真を撮らなければなりません。
I've been putting it together like this
こんな感じにまとめてみました
It's a bit like doing jigsaw puzzles on your mobile phone now
今では携帯電話でジグソーパズルをしているようなものです
come out and you can see
そうすれば外を見ることができます
How is there a line connected here?
ここにどうやって線がつながっているのでしょうか？
So let's say it's not connected well somewhere
それで、どこかがうまく接続されていないとしましょう
In fact, it is easy to check out with this S light.
実はこのSライト、チェックするのが簡単なんです。
So most of the packaging
したがって、ほとんどのパッケージは
is the PCB
PCBです
This is the motherboard company
こちらはマザーボード会社です
In fact, we have always had many companies
実際、私たちは常に多くの会社を持っていました
Wish we did this job for them
私たちが彼らのためにこの仕事をしてあげたらよかったのに
But even if these companies
しかし、たとえこれらの企業が
He won't give you too much money
彼はあなたにあまりお金をくれないでしょう
then ask you to do many things
それからあなたにたくさんのことをお願いします
actually those things
実際それらのこと
They can buy this machine by themselves
彼らはこの機械を自分で買うことができます
So we're mostly working on that as well
ですから、私たちも主にそれに取り組んでいます
That S light has one
S ライトには 1 つあります
There should be a lot of people doing it in the yard
庭でやっている人がたくさんいるはずです
By absorbing this S-Quam from outer space this universe
このS-Quamを宇宙から吸収することでこの宇宙は
Look at it at the time of the big bang
ビッグバンの時に見てください
Up to now, these astronomical problems
これまで、これらの天文学的な問題は、
Then why did I bring this up
ではなぜ私がこの話を持ち出したのか
That is to say, this detector
つまり、この検出器は
You want to detect X-ray and what we are doing X-ray is X-ray
あなたは X 線を検出したいと考えていますが、私たちがやっているのは X 線です。
we need to detect it
私たちはそれを検出する必要があります
It is very important to develop this detector in the middle
この検出器を途中で開発することが非常に重要です
Many of them come from here
彼らの多くはここから来ています
That has so many benefits but also many problems
それは非常に多くの利点がありますが、多くの問題もあります
For example like
たとえば次のように
Tell him this is the truth that I have been talking about
これが私が話してきた真実だと彼に伝えてください
sometimes is ugly
時々醜いです
It's just that the real world may not be as good as you think
ただ、現実の世界はあなたが思っているほど良くないかもしれません
but you can see through when
でもいつになるかはわかります
Then
それから
But the biggest problem is actually this
しかし最大の問題は実はこれです
OK so you can look at this
OK、これを見てください
Yeah I don't know you know what he's talking about
ええ、わかりません、彼が何のことを言っているのかわかりません
OK so why is this bad
OK、それではなぜこれが悪いのか
because I just told you
さっき言ったから
You still have the consideration of skin color
肌の色を考慮する必要があります
Yeah, I remember we were a while ago
ええ、少し前にいたのを覚えています
That is to say, at that time, I went with this professor Zhang Weihao
つまり、当時、私は張偉豪教授と一緒に行きました。
While in the US we visited a
アメリカ滞在中、私たちはある場所を訪れました。
Fellow of the American Academy of Sciences
アメリカ科学アカデミーフェロー
He said he would not go abroad
彼は海外には行かないと言いました
He said because he didn't want to be Scanned
彼はスキャンされたくなかったので言った
He said this Scan
彼はこのスキャンを言いました
He said according to his calculations
彼は自分の計算に従って言った
That is to say, there are thirty, twenty, forty in California
つまり、カリフォルニアには 30、20、40 あるということです。
He did that Scan once
彼はそのスキャンを一度実行しました
words like this
このような言葉
he did the math
彼は計算をしました
He thinks his Dose
彼は自分の用量を考えています
Do half CT with you
あなたと一緒にハーフCTをしましょう
Half tomography is the same
半分の断層撮影は同じです
yes ok
うんいいよ
So like this is what they put on
それで、これが彼らが着るものです
You people go this way, go over there and raise your hands high
君たちはこっちに行って、あっちに行って、手を高く上げて
you can get
得られる
And in this way they use the backlight
このようにしてバックライトを使用します
He didn't show you the bones
彼は骨を見せなかった
Because it's useless for him to look at your bones
骨を見ても無駄だから
He actually wants Scan to hit you
彼は実際にスキャンにあなたを殴りたいのです
will reflect
反映します
Those of us who studied Scan physics at that time
当時スキャン物理学を学んだ私たち
just feel weird
ただ奇妙に感じるだけ
why such a good idea
なぜそんなに良いアイデアなのか
we didn't think
私たちは考えませんでした
This is all understanding
これはすべて理解です
A business of several billion dollars
数十億ドル規模のビジネス
The reason is that his radiation dose is still very high
その理由は、彼の放射線量が依然として非常に高いためです。
only when they are for national security
国家安全保障のための場合のみ
didn't take it as a strict script
それを厳密な脚本とは考えなかった
So Europe bans this
だからヨーロッパはこれを禁止している
European airports do not have such scanners
ヨーロッパの空港にはそのようなスキャナーはありません
In the United States, they are now also changing
米国でも今、変化が起きています
Basically they end up with
基本的には次のようになります。
And like the American Academy of Sciences, they also wrote a letter to Obama
そして、アメリカ科学アカデミーと同じように、彼らもオバマに手紙を書きました。
say you are for national security
あなたは国家安全保障のためだと言う
you skip these things
あなたはこれらのことをスキップします
That is to say, if you really want to make a medical device
つまり、本当に医療機器を作りたいのであれば、
You just review these experiments
これらの実験を確認するだけです
just to give you this license
このライセンスを与えるためだけに
it could be years
何年もかかるかもしれない
But under the big hat of national security
しかし、国家安全保障という大きな帽子の下で
get it out
出してください
Then the company tells you about safety
その後、会社は安全性について説明します
just say safe
ただ安全だと言ってください
Then go in and do it
じゃあ入ってやってみろよ
so this is me in
これが私です
this is where you can see us
ここが私たちを見ることができる場所です
often pass like this
よくこうやって通り過ぎる
It's actually like him here
ここは実際に彼に似ています
X-ray
X線
I just told you why it's not good
なぜ良くないのかを言っただけです
you know this is a photo from long ago
これは昔の写真だとわかりますか
You can see him spawning XA here
ここで彼が XA を生成しているのを見ることができます
He's just over there looking happy
彼はただそこにいて幸せそうにしている
Yeah, I just said I hope they live less
ええ、私はただ彼らの命が短くなることを願っていると言いました
That's a wrong example
それは間違った例です
OK so now everyone
さて、それでは皆さん
Decades later, everyone found out that it is very simple
数十年後、誰もがそれが非常に単純であることに気づきました
Many people die very early
多くの人が早くに亡くなります
like this madame curie
このキュリー夫人みたいに
he is what he did
彼は彼がやったことだ
He didn't think of this thing at that time
彼はその時このことについて考えていませんでした
but later
でもその後
He started to get affected by the overhead beam
彼は頭上の梁の影響を受け始めた
like this too
これも好き
Then I'll show some more
それでは、さらにいくつかお見せします
It's the photo of this famous person's Ace Light
この有名人のエースライトの写真です
This was caught on the Internet
これはインターネットで拾ったものです
This is the president of the old Ross House in 1900
こちらは1900年の旧ロスハウスの社長です
He got a gunshot wound on him and hit a guy
彼は銃で撃たれて傷を負い、男を殴った
I heard he was beaten
彼が殴られたと聞いた
Just like our President Chen Zhiyuan
まさに我が国の陳志遠総統のように
After playing, he also gave a 90-minute TOP
プレー後は90分TOPもあげた
no feeling at all
全く感じない
only found out at the end
最後になって初めてわかった
OK, come here, there's already a
OK、ここに来て、すでに
There is another famous person, I think I should know about it after watching American cartoons
もう一人有名な人がいますが、アメリカの漫画を見てから知っておくべきだと思います
no, you can see him
いいえ、彼が見えます
And when I take it, you can see that X-ray has been used for organization
撮ってみると、組織化にX線が使われていることがわかります
We can look at his physical appearance, for example, I can see that his brain is very small
たとえば、彼の外見を見ると、彼の脳が非常に小さいことがわかります。
but i don't know what he's doing
でも彼が何をしているのか分かりません
So I don't want to say now, we can know what is in his mind, if we can know what he is thinking
だから今は言いたくない、もし彼が何を考えているかを知ることができれば、私たちは彼の心の中で何を考えているかを知ることができる
Then you can achieve the effect of the function, the function image
そうすれば、機能の効果、機能イメージを実現できます。
OK, there is another very famous X-ray, I dont know if you can recognize it
OK、もう一つ非常に有名な X 線写真があります。わかるかわかりませんが、
Called Tony Stark
トニー・スタークと呼ばれる
Then you can see that after he came out, his measurements reconstructed it
そうすれば、彼が出てきた後、彼の測定結果がそれを再構築したことがわかります。
You can look like this, this person I think you should probably know him
こんな風に見えるんだよ、この人はきっと知ってるはずだよ
OK, this is that one, and there is a famous X-ray
OK、これがそれです。有名な X 線写真があります。
Then this is Franklin
それからこちらはフランクリンです
This is the first X-ray image of DNA
これはDNAの最初のX線画像です
I think the deputy dean should be very clear
副学部長は明確にすべきだと思う
Everyone thought he should have won the Nobel Prize
誰もが彼はノーベル賞を受賞すべきだと思っていた
As a result, Jin Watson and Luke Tan took his picture away
その結果、ジン・ワトソンとルーク・タンが彼の写真を持ち去った
I wrote the result but didn't include it
結果を書きましたが、含めませんでした
This is a very famous X-ray
これは非常に有名なレントゲン写真です
but not like this
しかし、このようなものではありません
Choose to wrap
ラッピングを選択してください
X-ray was used and many other tasks were done
X線が使用され、その他多くの作業が行われました
like this is a i don't know what this is
これが何なのかわからない
But it's also famous
でもこれも有名ですよ
After you read it with X-ray
レントゲンで読み取ったら
They can see that actually inside
彼らは実際にそれを内部で見ることができます
Because if there is, you could have written it first
あるなら最初に書いたかもしれないから
Then you can change
そうすれば、あなたは変えることができます
So they can see in this way that he is actually another painting inside
このようにして、彼らは彼が実際に内側の別の絵であることがわかります
they later changed it all
彼らは後ですべてを変えました
Then there is another famous
それからもう一つ有名なのが
This is the mummy found in Egypt
これはエジプトで発見されたミイラです
This is what a cat looks like
猫ってこんな感じなんですね
But it actually has a hair wrapped in it
でも実際には髪の毛が巻かれているんです
this is his body
これは彼の体です
So these x-rays
それで、これらのX線写真は
When in use are standing in a shit
使用中はたわごとの中に立っています
that I can penetrate
浸透できるということ
I can also see inside
中も見えます
Can satisfy everyone's good habits
あらゆる人の良い習慣を満たすことができます
So how can I open this thing
それで、どうすればこれを開けることができますか
For example, people are a very troublesome thing
たとえば、人間というのはとても厄介なものだ。
people
人
I remember one time the Discovery Channel was saying
かつてディスカバリーチャンネルがこう言っていたのを覚えています。
19th century
19世紀
The greatest and most important medical method is the inner century
最も偉大で最も重要な医療法は内世紀である
This is the first time someone stuffed a mirror into your belly
誰かがあなたのお腹に鏡を詰め込んだのはこれが初めてです
can see inside
中が見える
It's very Fascinating
とても魅力的です
Trouble with people because of animals or people
動物や人による人間関係のトラブル
For example, if you want to see inside
例えば中を見たい場合
unless you kill it
あなたが殺さない限り
Now finally there is a thing that is
今、ついに、あることが起こりました。
i can watch while i'm alive
生きてる間は見れるよ
popular at the time
当時流行った
You can see this is also an old ad
これも古い広告であることがわかります
You can see them claiming to say
彼らがこう主張しているのがわかります
After taking a double photo, you won't have a headache
二重に写真を撮ったら頭が痛くなくなる
i think it might be
そうかもしれないと思う
You see this nerve has been injured
この神経が損傷しているのがわかります
But it's not impossible
でも不可能ではない
you can watch this now
今すぐこれを見ることができます
For example, our friend is in the mountains
たとえば、私たちの友達は山にいます
he gave me this
彼は私にこれをくれました
This is an active accelerator
これはアクティブアクセラレータです
It can produce fine X-rays like this coin
このコインのように細かいX線を生成できます
it's doing radiation therapy
放射線治療を行っている
Usually during radiotherapy
通常、放射線治療中
I'll just say I know there's a tumor here
ここに腫瘍があることは知っているとだけ言っておきます
I will follow
ついていきます
But when I take pictures, I don't want to take pictures of them all
でも写真を撮るときは全員を撮りたくない
nowhere else
他にはどこにもない
will make a cover
カバーを作ります
put this place
この場所に置いて
X-rays in other places are blocked
他の場所の X 線は遮断されます
I made a little progress later
その後少し進歩しました
I just don't want to do it once
一度だけはやりたくない
do it here
ここでやってください
Because X-rays don't tell the difference
レントゲンじゃ区別つかないから
all injured
全員負傷
I'll do a few more angles
もう少し角度を変えてみます
I can do 10 angles
10アングルもできるよ
Like it claims to be able to do these 1000 angles
1000 の角度を実現できると主張しているように
I know where your tumor is
あなたの腫瘍がどこにあるのか知っています
I move this coin
このコインを動かします
i've been following it
私はそれをフォローしてきました
The advantage is that when I was in cancer
利点は、私が癌だったとき
I can give it, for example, its dose of 1
たとえば、投与量 1 を与えることができます。
elsewhere it's
他の場所ではそれは
actually only one thousandth
実際には1000分の1だけ
If it uses a thousand of this projection
この投影を 1,000 個使用する場合
will effectively reduce the
を効果的に削減します
Radiation therapy to normal tissue
正常組織への放射線療法
So how could it work
では、どうすればうまくいくのでしょうか
but this is of course not
しかし、これはもちろんそうではありません
Image application
画像アプリケーション
But you also know like him
しかし、あなたも彼と同じように知っています
The most important part of this technology
この技術の最も重要な部分
In fact, its not that I made this detector to do this.
実際、これを行うためにこの検出器を作ったわけではありません。
another you locate
あなたが見つけた別の
Like for example he does a lot of these two treatments
たとえば、彼はこれら 2 つの治療をよく行っています
For example, you may be able to receive
たとえば、次のようなものを受け取ることができる場合があります。
because you are fixed
あなたは固定されているから
You have a small tumor on your body
体に小さな腫瘍がある
or a tumor of, say, a centimeter or two
または、たとえば 1 ～ 2 センチメートルの腫瘍
The person on you is moving and breathing
あなたのそばにいる人は動いて呼吸しています
So they have to have good video equipment nearby
したがって、近くに優れたビデオ機器が必要です
Usually when you go to a hospital there are two big x-ray machines
通常、病院に行くと大きなX線装置が2台あります。
Then under him is his detector
そして彼の下には探知機があります
he can at the same time
彼は同時にできる
Track your body's movements
体の動きを追跡する
Then when he set
それから彼がセットしたとき
he predictably said
彼は予想どおりこう言った
I'm now you're selling me like this
私は今、あなたが私をこのように売っているのです
or you breathe
あるいはあなたは息をします
he next time
彼は次回
Where will you move when he moves to this point?
彼がここまで引っ越したら、あなたはどこに引っ越しますか？
You are still making predictions
あなたはまだ予測を続けています
Speaking of this focus
このこだわりといえば
we mean
つまり
when doing imaging
イメージングを行うとき
For example, usually you do it in a hospital
たとえば、通常は病院で行われます。
I'll talk about why the hospital can't do it later
なぜ病院ができないかについては後ほどお話します
made these more detailed videos
これらのより詳細なビデオを作成しました
that image
そのイメージ
that reason is that
その理由はそれです
This quality of iShade
iShadeのこの品質
Its light source is of poor quality
光源の品質が悪い
That also has a better iShade light source
より優れた iShade 光源も備えています
I use a very small
私はとても小さいものを使っています
I let it focus called very small
極小というピントを合わせます
It produces a small spot of light
小さな光点を生成します
then we bring it
それから私たちはそれを持ってきます
for example look at this
たとえばこれを見てください
This IC
このIC
Check out this Madeleboa these
このマデルボアをチェックしてください
we actually
私たちは実際に
this is for
これがためのものです
It can be done without synchronous auxiliary test
同期補助テストなしで実行可能
can do it now
今すぐできます
then use this way
それからこの方法を使用してください
i'm talking about this
私はこれについて話しています
Before using the synchronous test
同期テストを使用する前に
I will talk about this project
このプロジェクトについて話します
This has nothing to do with audiovisual
オーディオビジュアルとは関係ありません
but what we recently did
でも私たちが最近したこと
because it's interesting
面白いから
And I think this will be of interest to everyone
そして、これは誰もが興味を持つと思います
that is to say this
つまりこれは言う
This is our latest
これは私たちの最新のものです
with our European
私たちのヨーロッパ人と一緒に
this collaborator
協力者
they are saying they are
彼らはそう言っている
this place is in venice
この場所はベニスにあります
Venice means they are a port
ヴェネツィアというと港です
from hundreds of years
何百年も前から
access to all their ports
すべてのポートへのアクセス
must have many files
多くのファイルが必要です
then this file
それからこのファイル
He could count millions, numbers like this
彼は何百万も数えることができた、このような数字
In a room like this, there might be thirty rooms like this
このような部屋には、このような部屋が 30 個あるかもしれません
So something like this would say
したがって、このようなことは言うでしょう
In fact, because he is not like the dead sea scripture
実際、彼は死海の経典のようなものではないので、
You just take one roll and I'll find a way to finish it
たった 1 ロール、それを終わらせる方法を見つけます
He has a lot so you don't want
彼はたくさん持っているから、あなたは欲しくないのです
It's not just about him being afraid of his damage
それは彼が自分のダメージを恐れているだけではありません
For example, you've been through something like this
たとえば、あなたは次のようなことを経験しました
Of course you don't want you to drive around
もちろん、車で走り回ってほしくないですよね
So of course there will be injuries when this is opened.
なので、これが開いたときに当然怪我が発生します。
But the most important reason is not this
しかし、最も重要な理由はこれではありません
Instead we want to be able to quickly put it into arcibe
代わりに、それをすぐに arcibe に入れられるようにしたいと考えています。
It's a bit like a digital power plant in our courtyard
それは私たちの中庭にあるデジタル発電所のようなものです
they just thought
彼らはただ考えただけだ
The people we worked with thought of doing it with X-rays
私たちが協力した人々は、X線を使ってそれを行うことを考えました
what is he going to do
彼は、何をしますか
He told me not to open the book
彼は私に本を開かないように言った
I lock up I do tomography
鍵を閉めて断層撮影をします
I do tomography
断層撮影を行っています
I can finally put the contents inside
ようやく中身を入れることができます
It is the way of reading without opening the book
本を開かずに読む方法です
You can grab all the text inside
内部のすべてのテキストを取得できます
Well, we've just started doing a little
そうですね、まだ少しやり始めたばかりです
This is actually pretty exciting
これは実際かなりエキサイティングです
Because now Venice has a very famous society
なぜなら今、ヴェネツィアには非常に有名な社会があるからです。
In vain
無駄に
When they invited us to do it in June
6月に彼らが私たちにそれをやろうと誘ったとき
They will go to a Public Event
彼らは公開イベントに行く予定です
Tell everyone that they are ready to officially start
正式に開始する準備ができていることを全員に伝えます
Later on their side
後で彼らの側に
if done well
うまくやれば
they will buy dozens
彼らは何十個も買うでしょう
The S2 machine like this
S2マシンはこんな感じ
put it on over there
そこに着てください
Scan it down for each one
それぞれについてスキャンしてください
We did some Pre-Limit results
プレリミットの結果をいくつか確認しました
I just want to say that this is a Mass manuscript I bought.
ただ言いたいのは、これは私が買ったミサ原稿だということです。
actually it's interesting
実際、それは興味深いです
that means i'm thinking right away
つまり、すぐに考えているということです
Why can't it be done in our hospital?
なぜ当院ではできないのでしょうか？
Or the Palace Museum
あるいは故宮博物院
the place of difference
違いの場所
this europe from
このヨーロッパから
Beginning less than a thousand years AD
西暦 1,000 年未満の始まり
while they were writing
彼らが書いている間
From the one called InkGull
InkGullというものから
it this is a number
これは数字です
count three removed things
取り除いたものを3つ数えます
a bit like jelly sauce
ちょっとゼリーソースっぽい
The compounded thing is this iron oxide particle
配合されているのはこの酸化鉄粒子です
So it has metal content in it
金属成分が入っているので
So X-ray can be seen
レントゲンが見えるので
The east is more advanced
東のほうが進んでるよ
Dongfang uses the Song Ni box is the carbon in the X-ray
東方は宋尼箱を使用していますが、これはX線の炭素です
there is no comparison
比較の余地はありません
So the way Europe looks like this
ヨーロッパはこんな感じです
It took almost a thousand years to a few years in the 1880s
1880年代にはほぼ千年から数年かかった
to the nineteenth century
19世紀まで
They only accepted the ink from the East after it came in
彼らは東洋からのインクを受け入れた後、それを受け入れた
They just started using this
彼らはこれを使い始めたばかりです
So the benefit is to become
したがって、利点は次のとおりです
We have so many hundreds of years of Windows
私たちには何百年にもわたる Windows があります
You can do it with SWIT
SWITでできるよ
Then we tried it and it turned out to be like this example
それで試してみたところ、この例のようになりました
This one is from 1566 and it's written on it
これは1566年のもので、そこに書かれています
this is its age
これがその年齢です
This Manual Script was first written in 1566
このマニュアルのスクリプトは 1566 年に初めて書かれました。
Then ours is visible light
それから私たちのものは可視光です
We will do S light now
これからSライトやります
we stack it
私たちはそれを積み重ねます
you can watch slowly
ゆっくり見ることができます
This is our S light video
これはSライトのビデオです
This Manual Script
このマニュアルのスクリプト
Unfortunately is very unfortunate
残念ながらとても残念です
mean it's inside
中にあるという意味です
we are talking
私たちは話しています
Our students are talking about our Posa
私たちの生徒たちは私たちのポサ​​について話しています
Said it was black heart ink
ブラックハートインクだと言った
Actually there's nothing in it
実は何も入っていないんです
what's this like
これはどんな感じですか
so you can see
それでわかります
Our paper sees clearly
私たちの論文でははっきりとわかります
but the paper can't see
でも紙には見えない
like this, good, like this
このように、良い、このように
You can see it, we're like stacking it directly on top of it
ご覧のとおり、その上に直接積み重ねているようなものです
You can see that the back is now S1 looking at this in the past
過去にこれを見ると後ろがS1になっているのがわかります
This is the image made by S1
これはS1が作成した画像です
So it means that at least this word can be developed
つまり、少なくともこの単語は開発できるということです
So it's important for me to come back and talk to people about developer
したがって、戻ってきて開発者について人々と話すことが私にとって重要です
You dont have a developer for this thing, no matter how good your image is in terms of resolution
画像の解像度がどれほど優れていても、この問題を扱う開発者はいません。
No matter how fast you are, it's useless
どんなに速くても無駄だ
So what becomes of this manipulating this developer
この開発者を操作するとどうなるでしょうか
It becomes a great knowledge, so generally this
大変な知識になりますので、一般的にはこれ
The medical imaging equipment, in the developer market
医用画像機器、開発者市場
Usually it accounts for one-third to one-half of its market
通常、市場の 3 分の 1 から 2 分の 1 を占めます。
Then we made a very simple simulation, because we can't afford it yet
まだ余裕がないので、非常に簡単なシミュレーションをしました。
Or you can't get the book, because we got a
あるいは、私たちが手に入れたので、あなたはその本を手に入れることができません
industrial stack it on top of each other and do the rotation
産業用に積み重ねて回転させます
Then let's try to solve this by hand
それでは、これを手動で解決してみましょう
After they are solved, they can be identified
解決したら特定できる
Then use this small X-ray code
次に、この小さな X 線コードを使用します
It is our laboratory that can buy it
購入できるのは当研究室です
It won't be very expensive to install
設置費用もそれほどかからないでしょう
we can already do it
私たちはすでにそれを行うことができます
For example, look at the cerebral blood vessels of this mouse
たとえば、このマウスの脳血管を見てください。
it's the whole brain the whole brain
それは脳全体です、脳全体です
so you can see
それでわかります
When there are not many diseases that can be identified here
ここで特定できる病気が少ない場合
didn't get what we wanted
私たちが望んでいたものは得られませんでした
but this is because
でもこれは
In this brain of your mouse
あなたのマウスのこの脳内で
let it hit this developer
この開発者にヒットさせてください
The same problem with developer
開発者にも同じ問題がある
That's not because of insufficient resolution
それは解像度が足りないからではありません
can look like this
このように見えることができます
You can see that we just made a few angles
いくつかの角度を付けただけであることがわかります
You can see how the distribution of its blood vessels looks like
血管の分布がどのように見えるかがわかります
OK, so what I want to tell you now is that
さて、私が今あなたに言いたいのは、
X-rays of these
これらのレントゲン写真
That is to say, no more than
つまり、それ以上ではありません
Most of us can now do
私たちのほとんどが今できることは、
But what I'm going to tell you now
でも、これからあなたに伝えようとしていることは、
That is to say, I actually said
つまり、実際にこう言ったのです
Is this this X-ray from your grandfather's time
これはおじいちゃんの時代のレントゲンですか？
That means we can be safe with this
つまり、これで私たちは安全になれるということです
ask any of this doctors
この医師の誰かに聞いてください
you talk to him
あなたは彼と話します
This X-ray can be compared
このレントゲンを比較することができます
he has absolutely no idea what you're talking about
彼はあなたが何のことを言っているのか全く分かりません
Then you can say can do
そうすれば、できると言えます
Of course he doesn't know about the elements and chemical composition
もちろん元素や化学組成などは知りません。
You see, it is said that 15 nanometers can be achieved
ほら、15ナノメートルが達成できると言われています
Or at this time he won't believe it
それとも現時点では彼は信じないだろう
But this is all because of what Fu Yuannan said just now.
しかし、これもすべて今の傅元南の発言のせいだ。
this synchrotron radiation
放射光
S-light produced by synchrotron radiation
放射光によるSライト
His quality is very good
彼の品質はとても良いです
That is to say, if you want to compare synchrotron radiation
つまり、放射光を比較するなら
It's kind of like a laser
レーザーっぽいですね
When imaging, especially the imaging of S light
撮影時、特にS光の撮影時
Say you're going to do
やると言ってください
I'll talk later
後で話します
Because this way we can do a comparison
こうすることで比較ができるので、
There are many different ways of comparing
比較する方法はたくさんあります
But the basic principle is that
しかし、基本的な原則は、
I these two materials like I would have been
この 2 つの素材を使用すると、
would give an example like your glass of water
コップ一杯の水のような例を挙げます
When you drink water you are in a bottle
水を飲むときはボトルの中にいる
If it is full, you cannot see its interface
いっぱいの場合はインターフェースが表示されません
You don't know it's you just look at it and don't touch it
触らないだけで見ているだけでは分からないのです
You don't know it's oil and water
それが水と油であることをあなたは知りません
but when you're half full
でも半分お腹がいっぱいになったら
you can see that surface
その表面が見えます
Why
なぜ
This is actually not because of absorption.
実はこれは吸収によるものではありません。
but because of refraction
でも屈折のせいで
Because its surface no matter what
どう見ても表面だから
Your visible light passes to your side
あなたの可視光はあなたの側に通ります
it has some folds
多少の折り目があります
you can watch it edge
あなたはそれを端で見ることができます
so you can tell it's water
だから水だとわかるよ
But today is full
でも今日は満席です
That is to say, its absorption of light by water
つまり、水による光の吸収です。
Absorption of visible light
可視光の吸収
Not much different from air
空気とあまり変わらない
so you don't have a mechanism that can image
画像を作成するメカニズムがありません
then we are now saying
それから私たちは今こう言っています
use this word
この言葉を使ってください
That is to say, S light affects different materials
つまり、S光はさまざまな物質に影響を与えます
It absorbs differently
吸い込み方が違います
That is to say, the absorption of bone and meat is of course different.
つまり骨と肉では当然吸収が違います。
But S only changes bones
ただし、S はボーンを変更するだけです
I have seen it for more than a hundred years
百年以上も見てきた
then you can't watch anything else
そうしたら他に何も見られなくなる
because of something else
何か別の理由で
Its absorption between the flesh and the flesh
肉と肉の間での吸収
Its absorption of S light
S光の吸収
are almost the same
ほぼ同じです
then we are thinking now
それから私たちは今考えています
if that is to say
それが言うなら
But these two organizations
しかし、この二つの組織は、
Its absorption of S light
S光の吸収
Although it is very close
とても近いのに
But its refractive index is not the same
しかし、その屈折率は同じではありません
The refractive index of S light is not the same
S光の屈折率は異なります
it's on the edge
それは端にある
will cause some refraction effect
何らかの屈折効果を引き起こします
You may have a chance to catch the edge of it
その先端を掴むチャンスがあるかも知れません
This is the so-called copper axial contrast
これはいわゆる銅軸コントラストです
The other is to get it in a different way
もう1つは、別の方法で取得することです
The refractive index of each material is different
それぞれの物質の屈折率は異なります
The so-called comparative
いわゆる比較論
Because when compared to the positive wave
なぜなら、ポジティブな波動と比較すると、
it affects its future
それはその将来に影響を与える
The future of the wave is because of your material
波の未来はあなたのマテリアルのおかげです
that is to say like the refractive index
つまり屈折率のようなものです
Is the refractive index that affects it
屈折率が影響するのか
There are several different ways
いくつかの異なる方法があります
It's all on X-ray now
今はすべてレントゲンで検査されています
These are known when visible light rises
これらは可視光が上昇するとわかります
Like Zernikey, Contra, Zernikey
ゼルニキー、コントラ、ゼルニキーのように
Wait for Wire Price in the 1950s and 1960s
1950 年代と 1960 年代の電線価格を待つ
Up to now, it can be done in XGrade
今のところ、XGradeで実行できます
i just told you
私はちょうどあなたに言いました
X-rays have the ability to distinguish elements
X線には元素を区別する能力がある
It also has the ability to distinguish its chemical composition
化学組成を識別する能力もあります
So we can use this way
したがって、このように使用できます
We look at the same iron
私たちは同じ鉄を見ます
inside the plastic
プラスチックの中に
We can know that this iron is not only
このアイアンは単なるものではないことがわかります。
And it's oxidized iron oxide
そしてそれは酸化された酸化鉄です
is to use this imaging method
このイメージング方法を使用することです
I will talk about the resolution later
解像度については後ほどお話します
Defresher image
デフレッシャ画像
This is relative to the current development of a new exchange
これは、新しい取引所の現在の開発に関連しています。
What we call X-ray finally has
私たちがX線と呼んでいるものは、ついに
This was the earliest when Ronald Reagan was president
これはロナルド・レーガンが大統領だったときに最も早いものでした
There is that new battle plan to do at the beginning
最初にやるべき新しい戦闘プランがあります
Only hope I get a really strong S-1
本当に強いS-1が得られることを祈るばかりです
You can just shoot the missile down
ミサイルを撃ち落とすだけでいい
or take down someone else's satellite
あるいは他人の衛星を破壊する
but it never worked out
しかしそれは決してうまくいきませんでした
But the concept of this is the development of this
しかし、これのコンセプトはこれの発展です
continues until now
今まで続いている
Now there are real lasers
今は本物のレーザーがある
I think we are now using an accelerator
今はアクセラレータを使用していると思います
Make this S-1 out
このS-1をアウトにしてください
it's like a laser
レーザーのようなものです
it has good coherence
それは良い一貫性を持っています
good destructive
良い破壊的
The application of this in the next few years
今後数年間でこれが応用される
i think it will come out slowly
ゆっくり出てくると思います
But it's just now
でもそれは今だけ
For example, the first such machine
たとえば、最初のそのようなマシンは
Started using it about two years ago at Stanford
スタンフォード大学で約 2 年前に使い始めました
four years
四年間
In Japan, it may have been used two years ago
日本では2年前に使われていたかもしれない
we now also hope
私たちも今は願っています
We are in Zhongyuanyuan
私たちは中原園にいます
be able to have some planning for using this aspect
この側面を使用するための計画を立てることができる
my own hope is to say
私自身の希望はこう言うことです
In 2015 we were able to
2015年に私たちはできました
Take this S-1 resolution
このS-1解像度を採用してください
are pushing further from Sunaimi to this road Nanami
スナイミからこの道をさらに突き進むナナミ
Then I have some nano
それからナノを持ってきます
There is an important development
重要な展開があります
It's like this image reconstruction method called tomography.
これはトモグラフィーと呼ばれる画像再構成法のようなものです。
when you do a normal tomography scan
通常の断層撮影スキャンを行うとき
while we are doing
私たちがやってる間
For example, my image
例えば私のイメージとしては、
I take an angle
角度をとります
Then I rotate this sample
次に、このサンプルを回転させます
or rotate your light source
または光源を回転させます
I took it variously for future
今後のために色々撮ってみました
I reconstructed it mathematically
数学的に再構成してみました
its three-dimensional entity
その三次元の実体
It used to be said that I wanted a lot from the angle I took.
撮った角度からすると「たくさん欲しい」と言われていました。
Because you take less angles
撮る角度が少ないから
you'll end up jumping
結局ジャンプしてしまうだろう
You have some places you will miss like this
こうやって見逃してしまう場所がいくつかあります
So becomes what you now assume
つまり、あなたが今想定していることになります
we usually do
私たちは通常そうします
We made this image at Statistical Services
この画像は統計サービスで作成しました
We may take 360 sheets
360枚お預かりする場合もございます
It means that we take, for example, a half-time
それは、例えばハーフタイムをとることを意味します。
Take 180 degrees
取180度
Or even you want more to get 1000
あるいは、さらに 1000 を獲得したい場合でも
But in the past, if it was used on humans
しかし、過去に人間に使用されていたとしたら、
Now generally used
現在一般用
They all want as little as possible
彼らは皆、できるだけ少ないことを望んでいます
The less I have this angle of this exposure
この露出角度が少なければ少ないほど
I can reassemble the best
最高のものを再び組み立てることができます
so i tried this
それで私はこれを試しました
A lot of people who are working on this side are doing this
こちら側で働いている多くの人がこれを行っています
This is a 2012 job
これは2012年の仕事です
they think they have a new way
彼らは新しい方法があると考えている
under conditions of little projection
突起が少ない条件下では
You can get a very good three-dimensional reconstruction
非常に優れた三次元再構成が得られます
let me mention this
これについて言及させてください
Because the collaborators of this group
なぜなら、このグループの協力者たちは、
It was called a theory with our chief Li Lingguo
それは私たちの責任者である李陵国との理論と呼ばれていました
he is also interested in this
彼もこれに興味があります
They just said they were doing some work on this
彼らはこれに関して何らかの作業を行っているとだけ言った
This is a breast tissue
これは乳房組織です
this place is kind of oil
ここは一種の油のような場所です
He can use very little dirt
彼は土をほとんど使わない
Very few projections can be made
実行できる予測はほとんどありません
Now during mammography
ただいまマンモグラフィー中
Basically he only does one
基本的に彼は一つしかやらない
They now have people say do tomothin fact
彼らは今、人々に事実を知ってもらうように言っています
He might be able to do some angles
彼はいくつかの角度を作ることができるかもしれない
They claim to do better
彼らはもっとうまくやると主張する
Alvation develop like this goes on
アルベーションはこうやって発展していく
Maybe after being so supernatural now
たぶん今はとても超自然的になってから
It is easy to get the structure of 3-dimensional space
3次元空間の構造を把握しやすい
It is of course helpful to judge them
もちろんそれらを判断することは有益です
when i see the two now
今二人を見たら
something in the middle
中間有東西
But his relative position
しかし、彼の相対的な位置は
For example, these small generalization points
たとえば、これらの小さな一般化ポイント
It correlates to the location of breast cancer judged by doctors
医師が判断した乳がんの位置と相関がある
still very helpful
まだとても役に立ちます
Many of their doctors would like to be able to do this
医師の多くはこれができるようになりたいと考えています
This is another TOMO SENSOR
こちらもTOMO SENSORです
I just use a few pictures to get results like TOMOGRAPHY
数枚の写真を使用するだけで、トモグラフィーのような結果が得られます
Like the result of broken seedlings
苗が折れた結果のように
In addition, some development is very important
さらに、いくつかの開発は非常に重要です
For example, the S-light detector
たとえば、S-light 検出器
S-light detector when we started doing S-light
S-light を始めた頃の S-light 検出器
We are thinking of using it on people
人に使用することを考えています
Definitely the best sensitivity
感度は間違いなく最高
But in fact, there are still technological developments
しかし、実際にはまだ技術開発が行われています
like i remember years ago
何年も前を思い出したように
When everyone uses a camera, it is still a CCD
誰もがカメラを使うとき、それはやはり CCD です
CCD is a kind of device
CCDはデバイスの一種です
No one is using CCD now
今は誰もCCDを使っていない
Now almost all are C-MOS detectors
現在はほぼすべてが C-MOS 検出器になっています
The X-ray detector only has different materials in the upper part
X線検出器は上部のみ材質が異なります
Mine is sensitive to S-light
私の場合はSライトに敏感です
but produces this
しかし、これを生成します
The way the signal is actually very close
信号が実際に非常に近い方法
that has another subscript
別の下付き文字がある
This is what we have in our lock now
これが今私たちの鍵の中にあるものです
Come to be the chairman and academician
会長兼学者になってください
Then this is of course ready-made
それから、これはもちろん既製品です
H&D type already available
H&Dタイプも販売中
But this company is the Swiss Syncertron
しかし、この会社はスイスのシンサートロンです
It has a kid team when it's ready
準備ができたら子供チームもできます
they turned it out
彼らはそれを証明した
So this is a very successful example
これは非常に成功した例です
I was originally because the scientists wanted to use
私はもともと科学者が使いたかったからです
I'm going to use this nice thing
この素敵なものを使わせていただきます
After getting it done, they found it very useful
完成させた後、彼らはそれが役に立ったと感じました
just went out and started a company
外に出て会社を始めたばかりです
The company is quite successful now
その会社は今ではかなり成功しています
a detector like this
こんな探知機
when he first came out
彼が初めて出てきたとき
their name is
彼らの名前は
One pixel one dollar
1ピクセル1ドル
So like this 6 million pixel
このように600万画素
it this Ding-san
それは丁さんです
It's Bohata down to about
くらいまではボハタです
Let's say $1 million
100万ドルとしましょう
like this
このような
Then this detector
それからこの検出器
He does everything
彼は何でもやってくれます
his usual place is
彼のいつもの場所は
a pixel in me
私の中のピクセル
I have an electronic system
電子システムを持っています
i've always been i've been like
私はいつもそうだった
put a small detector in the
小さな探知機を中に入れます
put it together
一緒に置く
Then his advantage is his predecessor
それなら彼の利点は前任者だ
put these things together
これらのものをまとめて
its noise will be less
そのノイズは少なくなります
So their detector claims to say
そこで彼らの探知機はこう主張する
we put it there
私たちはそこに置きます
like you now your CC
今のあなたのようにあなたのCC
your regular camera
いつも使っているカメラ
mobile phone camera
携帯電話のカメラ
when it's dark
暗いとき
why not
なぜだめですか
you soon it's noise
すぐにノイズになるよ
It has a lot of signal noise
信号ノイズが多い
you shoot longer
あなたはもっと長く撮影します
Noise overwhelms your image
ノイズが画像を圧倒する
like it this
これが好きです
you can shoot for half an hour
30分撮影できます
no noise
騒音なし
that of course
それはもちろん
That is to say, it is used for medical purposes.
つまり医療目的で使われているということです。
This imaging is very good
この画像はとても良いですね
why no one does
なぜ誰もやらないのか
then you will know why
そうすればその理由がわかるでしょう
that's too expensive
あれは高すぎる
then we know this company
それなら私たちはこの会社を知っています
Its IC is made in Taiwan
ICは台湾製です
because the world has only
世界にはそれしかないから
Taiwan's TSMC and UMC
台湾のTSMCとUMC
It can accept this small
この小さなものを受け入れることができます
Small quantity for this order
この注文の数量は少量です
So their IC is made in Taiwan
つまり、ICは台湾製です
so they just go out later
それで彼らは後で出かけるだけです
Plus their detector
さらにその探知機
The class of this material
この素材のクラス
That's so expensive
それはとても高価です
So after we made an appointment with the chairman
それで、会長と約束をした後、
he thinks this thing
彼はこのことを考えています
Taiwan should have no problem doing
台湾は問題なくやるべきだ
So we now have a program
これでプログラムができました
The director's office is that they made a similar detector a while ago
所長室は、少し前に同様の探知機を作ったそうです
The detector is in front of Japan
探知機は日本の目の前にある
they did deletronics
彼らはデレトロニクスをやった
Just cooperate with Japan's Free Latch on Laser
日本のレーザーのフリーラッチに協力してください
they took
彼らは取った
But after they took it, it seems that there is no afternoon
しかし、彼らがそれを取った後、午後はないようです
they said fine fine thank you
彼らは「大丈夫、大丈夫、ありがとう」と言いました
no more
もういや
It means that we are actually capable of doing this
つまり、実際にこれを行うことができるということです
Because they must be able to do it in Japan
日本ならできるはずだから
It's just that what they may do is not what we do
彼らがやることは私たちがやることではないというだけです
About X-rays related to Naimi
ナイミに関するレントゲンについて
I just used this example
私はちょうどこの例を使用しました
Manufacture of the first of our Nami components
最初のNamiコンポーネントの製造
It's the X-ray we just talked about
先ほど話したレントゲンです
We can do very high resolution
非常に高い解像度を実現できます
But the reason for this is why it couldn't be done before
しかし、これがなぜ今までできなかったのかというと、
It's because now we have the technology made by Nami
今はナミの作った技術があるからね
We can do X-ray optics
X線光学もできます
achieve very good resolution
非常に優れた解像度を達成する
In addition, we just told you
さらに、先ほどもお伝えしましたが、
X-ray resolution enhancement
X線解像度の向上
It's useless if you don't compare
比べないとダメだよ
I'll give you a piece of meat now
今から肉をあげます
Your resolution is as high as possible
解像度はできるだけ高くしてください
You put it under your S1 is white
S1の下に置くと白いです
you are useless
あなたは役に立たない
So to develop this nanoparticle
このナノ粒子を開発するには
The developing machine and the calibration machine are very important
現像機とキャリブレーション機は非常に重要です
before doing this
これを行う前に
It's useless for you to increase the resolution
解像度上げても無駄だよ
Then we say in another
次に、別の言い方で言います
we actually this
私たちは実際にこれを
At the same time, make this S1
同時に、これをS1にします
When you can see nanometer resolution
ナノメートルの解像度が見えるとき
We can also do a lot about this
これに関して私たちにもできることはたくさんあります
Natal technology
ネイタルテクノロジー
For example, we can study
たとえば、私たちは勉強することができます
When we are doing electroplating
電気めっきをしているとき
why is it better
なぜそれが良いのですか
it's not good to do that
それをするのは良くない
Usually you have to cut it
通常はカットする必要があります
It is very troublesome to use e-sports to watch
eスポーツを利用して観戦するのは非常に面倒
we can now at
今では、
Even when I'm electroplating
電気メッキをしているときでも
Just look at how long it is
どのくらいの長さなのか見てください
then adjust to its best condition
その後、最適な状態に調整します
so this is a feedback
これはフィードバックです
That's when we have this nice nano
そんなときにこの素敵なナノが登場します
When this detection technique
この検出技術が
It will also be helpful for our nano-manufacturing
私たちのナノ製造にも役立ちます
Then there is another one
それからもう一つあります
When we were doing this S1 imaging
この S1 イメージングを行っていたとき
The location of your sample
サンプルの場所
for example
例えば
Then I said to do this Tomography
それから私はこの断層撮影をするように言いました
I'm going to do this tomography
この断層撮影を行います
i let it turn
私はそれを回させました
There is no mechanical equipment
機械設備はありません
So it can be said that when I turn
だから、私が振り返ったとき、それは言うことができます
this thing
このこと
You now have our Naimi resolution images
これで、Naimi 解像度の画像が完成しました。
So the size of this whole
それで、この全体の大きさは、
Only 10micron
わずか10ミクロン
i just told you
私はちょうどあなたに言いました
Hair is 100micron
髪の毛は100ミクロン
it's your hair
それはあなたの髪です
One out of ten Full of you
10人に1人があなたでいっぱい
and now you have to turn something
そして今、何かを変えなければなりません
you want it this axis
この軸が欲しいの
stay here
ここで待ちなさい
mechanically impossible
機械的に不可能
so it becomes
そうなります
you zoom it in
あなたはそれをズームインします
when you turn
あなたが向きを変えるとき
This way this reorganized this
このようにしてこれを再編成しました
There is no way to do this calculation
この計算を行う方法はありません
So we have to try our best to find a way
だから私たちは最善を尽くして方法を見つけなければなりません
fix this problem
この問題を修正してください
One solution is to say
一つの解決策はこう言うことです
when i let it take a step
一歩踏み出させたら
I will tune
チューニングします
I need a good positioning
良いポジショニングが必要です
i know where it is
私はそれがどこにあるか知っています
After turning
回した後
I'll let it recalibrate
再調整させてもらいます
This is what we are currently doing
これが私たちが現在行っていることです
Before I talk about some practical examples
実際の例について話す前に
Then before I would
それなら私がそうする前に
Let me first tell you about this cooperator.
まずこの協力者について説明させてください。
I put it in yellow to be a physics person
物理派なので黄色にしました
That is to say, they make this equipment like me
つまり、彼らは私と同じようにこの装置を作っています
Then do this development
じゃあこの開発をしてみよう
including in Switzerland, in the U.S. and in South Korea
スイス、米国、韓国を含む
OK
OK
Then my own Team probably has so many people now
そうすると、私のチームには今、おそらく非常に多くの人がいるでしょう
Then the yellow one is the Queen of the National Society
じゃあ黄色いのはナショナル・ソサエティーの女王だよ
that's all we did
それが私たちがしたすべてです
You can see that the whole combination is our current Program
この組み合わせ全体が現在のプログラムであることがわかります。
The biggest goal of doing this Program is
このプログラムを行う最大の目標は、
I hope it can give us the same radiation as Taiwan.
台湾と同じ放射線を与えてくれる事を願っています。
The new accelerator
新しい加速器
A scientific project for this storage ring
このストレージリングの科学プロジェクト
This is what we are using now
これが私たちが今使っているものです
Called Taiwan Line Source
台湾ラインソースと呼ばれる
This is Taiwan's Photon Source
これは台湾の光子源です
If you have the opportunity to visit now
今訪れる機会があれば
This outer body is finished
これで外装は完成です
Thank you so much now
今では本当にありがとう
They may be hoping within the next year
彼らは来年以内にそうなることを望んでいるかもしれない
If users in Taiwan can start using it next year
来年台湾のユーザーが使い始められれば
The XFE I was talking about just now is the free electron laser
先ほど話したXFEとは自由電子レーザーのことです
This is an accelerator in Japan called SprayA
これはSprayAという日本の加速器です
It is the statistical radiation with the highest energy in the world
統計的には世界で最も高いエネルギーを持つ放射線です
And also a very good quality one
そして、非常に品質の良いものでもあります
This is their free electron laser
これが自由電子レーザーです
This length is about 700 meters
この長さは約700メートルです
So it takes 700 meters to accelerate this electron
つまり、この電子を加速するには700メートルかかる
Also after some processing
こちらも何らかの加工を施した上で
so that its final can produce very strong
そのため、最終的には非常に強力なものが得られます
It is a very short pulse
非常に短いパルスです
Say 50-50 Fantlose Second
50-50 ファントローズ 2 番目と言う
Fantlose Second is better than Pico in...
Fantlose Second は Pico よりも優れています...
OK is Nano and below is Pico
OKはNano、下はPicoです
Pico is Fantlose again
ピコは再びファントローズです
Each is 1000 times worse
それぞれが1000倍悪い
So it's this...
それで、これです...
Time is it, this wave is a very short pulse
時間です、この波は非常に短いパルスです
In such a short pulse
あんなに短いパルスで
synchrotron radiation
放射光
A Pulse height is almost 12 defenses
パルスの高さはほぼ12ディフェンスです
Akiko Tamaki
多的晃子
So this light is very, very strong
だからこの光はとてもとても強いです
and in a short time
そして短時間で
So you can do some work related to time
時間に関係する仕事ができるようになります
Video Programmers basically hope to use X-Ray to cover
ビデオ プログラマーは基本的に、X-Ray を使用してカバーすることを望んでいます。
to compensate for high-resolution, very high-resolution gaming
高解像度、非常に高解像度のゲームを補うため
What can be done with general medical imaging
一般的な医用画像処理で何ができるのか
i was hoping to talk
話したいと思っていた
I see like this when we should stop
やめるべき時はこう見えます
Because each of these is an example of my own development
これらはそれぞれ私自身の開発の一例であるため、
i just told you
私はちょうどあなたに言いました
maybe today i know this maybe probably enough
おそらく今日はこれで十分だと思います
this is caused
これが原因です
I feel like if I had a light come in
光が入ってきたような気がする
there is an edge here
ここにエッジがある
you will deflect the light slightly
光をわずかにそらします
so you're going to make this edge look like it's not
このエッジをそうでないように見せます
If it was here, it would have absorbed so much
ここにあったらたくさん吸収できたのに
Here now it has a little bit of contrast
ここには少しコントラストがあります
But after this part like this
しかし、この部分の後にはこんな感じ
After the change, the contrast will be stronger
変更後はコントラストが強くなります
Here is an example of a practical calculation
実際の計算例は次のとおりです
Then you can see that this is the actual image
これが実際の画像であることがわかります
When I have a something like
私が何かを持っているとき
Here will produce very bright bright text
ここでは非常に明るい明るいテキストが生成されます
then i have one
それなら私は一つ持っています
demonstration
デモンストレーション
like this is
これのように
these are two rays
これらは 2 つの光線です
you can see it this distance
この距離でも見えるよ
When the distance from the detective is getting longer and longer
探偵との距離がどんどん遠くなっていくとき
this edge will
このエッジは
at one stage it becomes very apparent
ある段階ではそれが非常に明らかになる
like this
このような
After a long time, it began to blur again
長い時間が経つとまたぼやけ始めた
This is the most suitable time in its midst
今がその真っ只中に最適な時期です
It is very powerful to use it as an image.
画像として使用すると非常に効果的です。
if you could have seen me go back to the beginning
私が最初に戻るのを見ていたなら
at the very beginning
一番最初に
You see, the edge is actually faint
ほら、実はエッジが薄いんです
you can't see
あなたには見えません
But just taking this image alone
ただ、この画像だけ撮っても
This sample and your image
このサンプルとあなたの画像
Whether it's negatives or not
ネガティブであろうがなかろうが
CGD is also good
CGDもいいですね
pull it away
それを引き離す
You can see its image slowly coming out
そのイメージが徐々に出てくるのがわかります
that's what we're talking about
それが私たちが話していることです
One of the best demonstrations of Face contact
フェイスコンタクトの最良のデモンストレーションの 1 つ
For example, at one centimeter
たとえば、1センチのところで
it will see very well
とてもよく見えるでしょう
It's clear that even these shafts in his middle
彼の真ん中のシャフトさえも明らかに
can see clearly
はっきりと見える
what's so important about this
これの何がそんなに重要ですか
It's when you see your x-ray in the hospital
病院でレントゲンを見たときのことです
that radial it will make you cling
そのラジアルはあなたにしがみつくでしょう
The reason for the tight fit is simple
ぴったりフィットする理由は単純です
I have one of these light sources today
今日はこれらの光源の 1 つを持っています
X-ray is a shadow graph
X線は影のグラフです
just look at the shadow
ただ影を見てください
so i put my hands here now
だから今ここに手を置いた
light source like you now
今のあなたのような光源
Your edge must not be...
あなたのエッジはそうではありません...
But if you go outside
でも外に出ると
if you go to see the sun
太陽を見に行くなら
you are so chic
あなたはとてもシックです
have you ever wondered why
なぜだろうと思ったことはありますか
It's because the light source is too diffuse
光源が拡散しすぎるためです
because it borders
国境を接しているから
There are photos here
ここに写真があります
So you can draw straight lines
直線を引くことができるので、
you'll know it's edge
それがエッジだとわかるだろう
will be fully illuminated
完全にライトアップされます
So say this way
だからこう言ってください
That is to say, even if you are on the edge
つまり、たとえ限界にいたとしても、
have this strengthening effect
この強化効果がある
also be affected by the poor quality of your light source
光源の品質の悪さの影響も受けます
wash it off
それを洗い流します
so at this time
だからこの時点では
that is usually
それは通常です
You want it to be brimless
つばなしにしてほしい
you hope higher
あなたはもっと高いことを望んでいます
so you can watch
だからあなたは見ることができます
My shadow is getting clearer and clearer
私の影はますます鮮明になっていきます
By this time the edges are clear
この時点でエッジは明確になります
then it is very simple
それはとても簡単です
You can know this geometry
この幾何学模様を知ることができます
then we now
それから私たちは今
But the problem is that we were just talking about
しかし、問題は、ちょうど私たちが話していたことです
This refraction is also different
この屈折も違う
refract me when a thing passes by
何かが通り過ぎるときに私を屈折させてください
Its refraction is to deflect this angle
その屈折はこの角度を変えることです
is the difference in your refractive index
屈折率の違いです
Into justice
正義の中へ
at small angles
小さな角度で
So its refractive index
したがって、その屈折率は
This S light all things
このSはすべてのものを照らします
There is very little difference with air
空気との差はほとんどない
is the square of ten
は10の2乗です
is the refractive index of its air
は空気の屈折率です
if one
1つあれば
has the refractive index of water
水の屈折率を持っています
We are 1.0001
私たちは1.0001です
One ten-thousandth of 0.99994
0.99994 の 10,000 分の 1
or one in a hundred thousand
または10万分の1
So denoting its deflection pilot
つまり、偏向パイロットを意味します
you now make a ball
あなたは今ボールを作ります
a water ball
ウォーターボール
or a glass ball
またはガラス玉
When this S light passes through
このS光が通過すると
It deflects at a very, very small angle
非常に小さな角度で偏向します
But we want to see its edge imaging
しかし、私たちはそのエッジイメージングを見たいのです
what are you going to do
何をする？
very simple
とてもシンプルな
I will pull the distance away
距離を縮めていきます
Originally it was this deflection, this Chen Xiaolou
元々はこの偏向、この陳暁楼でした
pull it away
それを引き離す
Zoom in on the resolution of my detector
検出器の解像度を拡大してください
start can catch say
スタートは言うことをキャッチできます
I have light and dark spots on the edges
端に明るい点と暗い点があります
The shape of the whole thing will be highlighted
全体の形状が強調されます
But if you don't have a good light source
ただし、適切な光源がない場合は、
you have a problem
あなたには問題があります
You zoom out and your image becomes blurred
ズームアウトすると画像がぼやけてしまいます
it washes the edge off
それはエッジを洗い流します
So this is why we now
だからこそ私たちは今、
we are what we are
私たちは私たちそのものです
I was talking about this Face Country ten years ago
私は10年前にこのフェイスカントリーについて話していました
We also had a press conference
記者会見も行いました
At that time everyone asked me
その時みんなが私に尋ねました
When can Face Country be used in the hospital?
フェイスカントリーはいつ病院で使用できますか?
let's say five years
5年としましょう
It's been ten years now
もう10年になります
You're asking me maybe I can still talk for five years?
あなたは私に、もしかしたら5年はまだ話せるのではないかと尋ねているのですか？
that is to say, where is the reason
つまり、その原因はどこにあるのか？
That is, we except the synchronous subsidiary
つまり、同期子会社を除いた当社は、
Besides such a good light source
このような優れた光源に加えて、
I can't find any other substitute students
他に補欠生徒が見つからない
I just told you that
先ほど言ったばかりです
I am actually our light source
実は私は私たちの光源なのです
The first is that it requires collimation to be a bit
1 つ目は、コリメートを少し行う必要があることです。
We only need its light source to be small enough
光源が十分小さいことだけが必要です
So today I put a
それで今日私は
put in a fight
喧嘩の後
put it on an open eye put it on
開いた目にそれを置きます
This light source is like a point
この光源は点のようなものです
You can see that the edges will be very clear
エッジが非常に鮮明になっていることがわかります
The only problem is when you put
唯一の問題は、いつ入れるかです
You have no intensity, you have no light
あなたには強さがないし、光もない
light becomes a little bit
光が少しずつ明るくなる
The advantage of synchrotron radiation is that
放射光の利点は、
My light source is very small but it's very collimated
私の光源は非常に小さいですが、非常に平行です
is that I can send one like we do now
今と同じように送れるということです
Our light source represents 100mc
私たちの光源は100mcを表します
as thick as hair
髪の毛ほどの太さ
placed 30 meters away
30メートル離れたところに設置
When you look at it with the naked eye, it looks like a point light source
肉眼で見ると点光源のように見えます
But it sends the light to you when you need it
でも必要なときに光を送ってくれる
it won't spread
それは広がらないでしょう
You can think of me if a single point light source
単一の点光源なら私を思い浮かべてください
It is 1 over R squared
Rの2乗の1です
It says to follow the distance of R
Rの距離をたどってくださいと書かれています
When you walk 30 meters away, its already gone
30メートル歩くともう消えてる
this is what we've been waiting for
これが私たちが待っていたものです
hope you say there is a good light source
良い光源があると言っていただければ幸いです
this has always been
これはいつもそうだった
Many people have always thought
多くの人がずっと考えてきた
can be done in this way
この方法で行うことができます
but we waited so long
でも私たちはとても長い間待ちました
Actually quite disappointed
実際かなりがっかりしました
That is to say, now
つまり、今、
so far very few
これまでのところ非常に少ない
This is an example
これは一例です
That's what they do with hair radiation
それが毛髪放射線治療でやっている事だ
I have separate comparative
別途比較記事があります
Just do a separate five-party photography
別途5人で写真撮影すればいいだけ
what difference would you make
どのような違いがありますか
this is not
これではありません
It is conventional
従来のものです
Tradition
伝統
This is done with face contrast mammography
これは顔面造影マンモグラフィーで行われます
you can see
見ることができます
Of course, this place also stands out
もちろんここも目立つ
It's not because of its Western state differences
それは西部州の違いのせいではない
This is made by a Japanese Konika
これは日本のコニカが作ったものです
They are also called face contrast mammography
顔面造影マンモグラフィーとも呼ばれます
but this
しかしこれは
Has not been used by many people
あまり人に使われていない
we're asking general practitioners
私たちは一般開業医に尋ねています
They don't even know it exists
彼らはそれが存在することさえ知りません
so i was thinking
それで私は考えていました
is the benefit it may get
それが得られるかもしれない利益です
Not as much as they advertise
彼らが宣伝しているほどではない
So doctors don't have much interest in doing this
だから医者はこういうことにはあまり興味がないんだよ
The face contrast mammography
顔面造影マンモグラフィー
Let me give another very simple example
もう一つの非常に単純な例をあげましょう
like this
このような
this is
これは
This is the heart of a mouse
これはネズミの心臓です
a part
一部
at this distance
この距離で
you look like
あなたは次のように見えます
In fact, so-and-so tiger
実際のところ、まあまあ、フフ
this black place
この黒い場所
is inside its heart
その心の中にある
we specifically make it
私たちは特別にそれを作ります
This structure that grows lidification
蓋化を生むこの構造
capping structure
キャッピング構造
just to come
ただ来るだけ
Simulate this non-coming situation
この来ない状況をシミュレートする
because the mice didn't come in
ネズミが入ってこなかったから
Although you use its breast cancer cells
乳がん細胞を使用しているにもかかわらず
But you can't grow breast cancer like a human
しかし、人間のように乳がんを成長させることはできません
Therefore, it cannot be used as an example of video
したがって、ビデオの例として使用することはできません。
But here we do
しかし、ここではそうします
with different distances
異なる距離で
You go to see me just to distance you
あなたは距離を置くためだけに私に会いに行きます
You can look at these structures and suddenly run out
これらの構造を見て、突然走り出すことができます
see clearly
はっきり見える
Then this is the biggest benefit of doing this Face Contrast
これがこのフェイスコントラストを行う最大の利点です
like this too
これも好き
You see, after the distance is extended
ほら、距離が伸びたら
its image is very clear
そのイメージは非常に鮮明です
For example, what I just said just now is that
たとえば、今私が言ったことは、
You can see that these two are actually poor in contrast.
この 2 つは実際には対照的に貧弱であることがわかります。
not so much
それほど多くない
But because of the efficiency of refraction at the edges
しかし、端での屈折効率のため、
After the effect, you can see its edge very clearly
エフェクト後はエッジがはっきりと見えます
Then you can see that we use this way
そうすれば、このように使用していることがわかります
You can see this bubble above
上にこのバブルが見えます
In fact, it is the structure of the metal that grows
実際、成長するのはこの金属の構造です。
because it has metal connections with electrical connections
電気接続と金属接続があるため
ok
Ok
Okay, the rest of the following are some demonstrations
さて、以下の残りの部分はいくつかのデモンストレーションです
Then here are some comparisons we made with fossils
次に、化石との比較をいくつか示します。
not much relationship
あまり関係がない
But the business name is important
でも店名は大事だよ
So Polish is in Size
ポーランドのサイズは大きい
ok
Ok
Here's another job we did
これが私たちが行ったもう一つの仕事です
even it was a long time ago
たとえそれがずっと前のことだったとしても
Fossil of this embryo from 540 million years ago
5億4千万年前のこの胚の化石
Then this is our relationship with Professor Li Jiawei of Tsinghua University
それでは、これが清華大学の李佳偉教授との関係です。
when cooperating
協力するとき
He said he found a lot of these sheds in here
彼はここでこのような小屋をたくさん見つけたと言いました
this is a fossil
これは化石です
this fossil is small
この化石は小さいです
Because it's an embryo kind of like that Kentin
ケンティンみたいな胎児だから
For example, when the coral is spawning,
たとえば、サンゴが産卵するとき、
Then this is in the southwest of the mainland
そして、これは本土の南西部にあります
That is when the geological movement
そのとき、地質学的動きが起こります。
may be spawning in this
この中に産卵しているかもしれない
Others suddenly the earth's crust becomes passive
突然地殻が活動的になる人もいます
all frozen in time by all these things
これらすべてのことによってすべてが時間の中で凍結されました
come out like this
こうやって出てくる
Then the size of this one is about
そうすると、このサイズは約
550.5 This is useless
550.5 これは役に立たない
OK then we did a lot more
OK、それではもっとたくさんのことをしました
early days
初期
Like this fly head
このハエの頭のように
I put it where we say
私たちが言うところにそれを置きます
Because this is actually a beautiful picture of clam worms
これは実際にはハマグリの虫の美しい写真だからです
That is to say, the whole head of a fly
つまり、ハエの頭全体
you can tell it's inside
中にあることがわかります
So I have the structure of the first detail
最初の詳細の構造ができました
But like this we can
しかし、このようにして私たちはできるのです
Reconstructed tomography
再構成断層撮影
you can see his head very clearly
彼の頭がはっきりと見えます
But you say it's nothing
でも君は何もないと言う
with this electron microscope
この電子顕微鏡を使って
You can see clearly with this scanning electron microscope
この走査型電子顕微鏡ではっきりと見ることができます
But what the SEM can't do is
しかし、SEM にできないことは、
he can't see inside yet
彼はまだ中が見えない
So we can reorganize
それで組織を再編成できる
we can do whatever
私たちは何でもできます
because it's a model
モデルだから
Although this is a model
これはモデルですが
This is a very accurate model
これは非常に正確なモデルです
It is the model with the same resolution as yours
あなたと同じ解像度のモデルです
after you make it
作った後は
you can go in any direction
どの方向にも進むことができます
Just like you did this tomography in the hospital
病院でこの断層撮影をしたのと同じように
you don't need to stay there anymore
もうそこにいる必要はありません
From now on, he keeps looking at this picture of him
これからも彼は自分のこの写真を見続ける
He can find where he wants to look
彼は見たい場所を見つけることができる
ok
Ok
there's some of this
これのいくつかがあります
wow
おお
Then I won't talk about how I did it
じゃあどうやってやったかは話さないよ
I'm in this now
私は今この中にいます
we have to advertise
私たちは宣伝しなければなりません
We're going to do a good resolution
しっかり解決していきます
I just said that
私はちょうどそれを言いました
video like this
このようなビデオ
Your resolution is up to you on this catapult
このカタパルトでの決断はあなた次第です
today i will take this with me
今日はこれを持って行きます
Take a CCD to do it
CCDを使ってそれを行う
It shines at this time, because your light has a very short wavelength
このとき光るのは、あなたの光の波長が非常に短いからです
I just said that after the light passes through
光が通った後って言ったばかりだよ
This image does not cause resolution issues
この画像は解像度の問題を引き起こしません
But at this time the resolution is limited to your detector
ただし、現時点では解像度は検出器に制限されています
So I take a CCD one by one
なのでCCDを一枚ずつ撮っていきます
You said above that I am sensitive to S-light CCD
上で私は S-light CCD に敏感だと言いましたね
When you go, your pixel determines your resolution
ピクセルが解像度を決定します。
So today if you talk about this semiconductor company
さて、今日この半導体会社について話すとしたら、
This CCD can be made into a CMOS
このCCDはCMOS化可能です
is this pixel with 20 nanometers
このピクセルは20ナノメートルですか
My resolution is 20nm
私の解像度は20nmです
this do s light
これは軽いです
But this can't be done now
でも今はそれができない
Now look at the specifications of your cameras
次にカメラの仕様を見てみましょう
About two or three microns
2～3ミクロンくらい
So this is actually what we do and that
これが私たちが実際に行っていることです
Then the other way is my S light
じゃあ反対側は私のSライトです
Can't I zoom in on it first
まずは拡大してみませんか
I'll use this detector to pick it up again
この探知機を使ってまた拾うよ
like this
このような
Because you said I am zooming in
ズームインしてるって言ったから
It will not affect the resolution of your intrinsic itself
組み込み関数自体の解決には影響しません
Then I am at this time, you are originally a micron resolution
じゃあ私は今、あなたは本来ミクロンの解像度なのよ
If I enlarge the resolution to 20 times
解像度を20倍に拡大すると
i can get 20 times
20回はもらえるよ
It becomes 50nm 50nm resolution
50nm 50nmの解像度になります
why do you do that
どうしてそれをするの
The reason is that the S-light Lens is very, very difficult to make
その理由は、S-light レンズの製造が非常に難しいためです。
Because S light penetrates everything
S光は全てを貫くから
it is not pleated
プリーツではありません
You take one through it and it ignores you
あなたがそれを通過しても、それはあなたを無視します
Then you want the other reflective way
次に、別の反射的な方法が必要になります
it's slightly angled
少し斜めになっています
it just goes through
それはただ通過するだけです
so it becomes very difficult to do
だからそれをするのは非常に難しくなる
The only device that everyone agrees is better
誰もが同意する唯一のデバイスがより優れています
That is, if you are on the bus
つまり、バスに乗っている場合
Sometimes there is a magnifying glass behind the bus
時々バスの後ろに虫眼鏡があります
It looks like a ring
指輪みたいですね
That's the Fone Lens we're talking about
それが私たちが話しているFoneレンズです
that part
その部分
how well that thing is done
それがどれほどうまく行われているか
depends on your resolution
あなたの解像度に依存します
The size of its outermost circle is related to your resolution
一番外側の円のサイズは解像度に関係します
then i just said
それから私はちょうど言いました
If we reach the best 15nm
最高の15nmに到達したら
that outer circle
その外側の円
We want to achieve a line block of almost 20nm
ほぼ20nmのラインブロックを達成したい
Then at 20nm it has to be very high
20nmでは非常に高くなければなりません
Because you want to have an effect on S light
S光に効果を与えたいから
you are going to build a wall
あなたは壁を築くつもりです
For example, a height of 500 nanometers
たとえば、高さは 500 ナノメートルです。
But the width of 20 nanometers
ただし幅は20ナノメートル
Then you still use gold to fill it up
その後もそれを埋めるためにゴールドを使用します
So the difficulty of this is very high
なので難易度はかなり高いです
I'd say we've challenged before
以前にも挑戦したことがあると思います
For example, we are supplying TSMC
たとえば、TSMC に供給しています。
I said we TSMC, you can't do this
私たちはTSMC、あなたにはそんなことはできないと言いました
Because TSMC they made this device
TSMCがこのデバイスを作ったからです
Can do ten or twenty nanometers
10ナノメートルや20ナノメートルも可能
But its S5 ratio is very low
しかし、S5比率は非常に低いです
And they do ten or twenty nanometers
そして彼らは10ナノメートルか20ナノメートルを行います
It's the FaceShift way
それはFaceShiftのやり方です
It can't do Grading
グレーディングはできません
That is to say, I can't do continuous
つまり連続はできない
Twenty empty twenty results like this
このような 20 の空の 20 の結果
It can only say I do a big one like this
こんな大きなことをやるとしか言えない
Edge I can do it well done it becomes like that
Edge できるよ、よくできた、そうなる
Then the device made is
そこで作った装置は、
because we have a really nice nike process inside the lock
なぜなら、ロックの内側には本当に素晴らしいナイキのプロセスが施されているからです。
that this is this is a
これはこれです
that is to say we are saying
つまり私たちはこう言っているのです
Rarely have this one this in the whole world
世界中でこれほどのものはめったにありません
A department like this can look like this
このような部門は次のようになります
equipment like this
このような装備
then we are lucky too
それなら私たちも幸運です
There is this thing to support us
私たちをサポートしてくれるものがあります
So we made this Device like this
そこでこのデバイスを次のように作りました
Then come as a magnifying glass
それから虫眼鏡として来てください
This is the magnifying glass of S1
こちらはS1の拡大鏡です
When this S1 passes by
このS1が通り過ぎる時
you use this magnifying glass
あなたはこの虫眼鏡を使います
Then project it onto this CCD
そしてそれをこのCCDに投影します
Your resolution is
あなたの決意は
Divide your resolution by
解像度を次の値で割ります
your magnification
あなたの倍率
Then make this Device
次に、このデバイスを作成します
I just said like this
こう言っただけです
This is the outermost circle inside
これは内側の一番外側の円です
smallest possible
可能な限り最小の
We can do 20nm
20nmもできる
Its height is 450nm
その高さは450nmです
Then this is with gold seat
続いてこちらはゴールドシート付き
Because the absorption of gold is the strongest
金の吸収が一番強いので
Then it's the best time to do it
それならそれをやるのに最適な時期です
just like
と同じように
This is a Lens that looks like this
こんな感じのレンズです
to make an image
イメージを作る
Like this is our test
これが私たちのテストのようです
What a pattern test looks like
パターンテストはどのようなものですか
the innermost one
一番奥の
each of this structure
この構造のそれぞれが
is this interval of 30nm
この間隔は30nmですか
So we can clearly see
だから私たちははっきりと見ることができます
means that our resolution
それは私たちの決意を意味します
Should be better than 30nm
30nmよりも優れているはずです
So we did another
それで私たちは別のことをしました
His test is like we made a structure ourselves
彼のテストは私たちが自分たちで構造物を作ったようなものです
The innermost is 20nm
一番内側は20nm
You can see that this is actually a good result
これは実際に良い結果であることがわかります
It's good to be able to parse it out
非常によく解析できます
It means that our resolution should still be better than 20nm
これは、解像度が依然として 20nm よりも優れている必要があることを意味します。
So we put a lot of effort into doing
そのため、私たちは次のことに多くの労力を費やしました
Finally decided to say that we look at it with a different structure
最終的には、別の構造で見ると言うことにしました
Let's look at his analysis
彼の分析を見てみましょう
calculated in a strict way
厳密な方法で計算された
So our resolution is about 16nm
したがって、解像度は約16nmです
16nm
16nm
This means that we are doing X-ray like this now
ということは、今このようなX線検査を行っているということです。
Still no one can do a structure like this
こんな構造はまだ誰も出来ない
I give an example
例を挙げます
We originally published an article a while ago
元々は少し前に記事を公開しました
We actually started doing this structure in 2006
実際にこの構造を作り始めたのは 2006 年です
Resolution from earliest to last
最初から最後までの解決策
Come down from the secular generation, the Mishi, and the eleventh degree
還俗、壬氏、十一位
We can do it for about 16 years now
これで16年くらいはできるかな
In fact, since this
実はこれ以来、
In fact, we are of course proud to say that
実際、私たちはもちろん誇りを持ってこう言えます。
from this onwards
これから
a world structure
世界構造
it no one can do like this
こんなことは誰もできない
So we used the equipment of the middle actor all the way
なので、真ん中の俳優の機材をずっと使いました
do it now we are
今やってください、私たちは
Now we can do this to the extent that this has become
これで、ここまでできるようになりました。
OK
OK
I'll just skip the part about rice granules
米粒の部分だけ省略します
I'm at the end
もう終わりだ
Let me show you a few examples
いくつかの例をお見せしましょう
I don't explain like this is a
これがそうだというようには説明しません
Let's do a lower resolution version of this
これの低解像度バージョンを作ってみましょう
you think
あなたは考える
OK
OK
This is an example of our cooperation with these three Chengan physicians
これは、これら 3 人の成安医師との協力の一例です。
That is to say, he is studying this long-term kidney disease
つまり、彼はこの長期にわたる腎臓病を研究しているのです。
I think you probably know why we study long-term kidney disease
私たちが長期の腎臓病を研究する理由はおそらくご存知だと思います
Because Taiwan is the devil king of kidney dialysis
台湾は腎臓透析の魔王だから
Kidney dialysis alone will wash away 80 billion
腎臓透析だけで800億人が洗い流される
So and most of the reasons are
そして、その理由のほとんどは次のとおりです
Go and take those medicines that invigorate the kidneys
腎臓を元気にする薬を飲みに行ってください
Caused
原因
OK
OK
This is a normal small genus of kidney
これは正常な小さな腎臓の属です
You can see it every one of this kidney bulb
この腎臓の球根一つ一つがそれを見ることができます
The glomerulus can be seen clearly
糸球体がはっきりと見える
blood vessels are fine
血管は大丈夫です
every one is clean
誰もがきれいです
so you can see the secret mama
そうすればママの秘密がわかるよ
we can even say
私たちも言うことができます
This whole little one is like this
この小さなもの全体はこんな感じです
Its glomeruli may have seven to eight thousand
その糸球体には 7 ～ 8,000 個ある可能性があります
But if you say like this example
でも、この例のように言うと
That is to say, this is a disease they created.
つまり、これは彼らが作り出した病気です。
It's called a long-term kidney disease in this mouse.
このマウスでは長期腎臓病と呼ばれています。
You can see that most of the glomeruli are gone
糸球体のほとんどが消失しているのがわかります。
only a small part remains
ほんの一部しか残っていない
because it if not
そうでなければ
the mouse won't live
ネズミは生きられない
Most of the glomeruli have disappeared
糸球体のほとんどが消失している
It doesn't matter if it is inflamed
炎症を起こしても関係ない
or it is blocked
もしくはブロックされている
Then there are only these water-quality blood vessels in the middle
すると真ん中にあるのはこの水質の血管だけです
Contains only a small portion of this kidney
この腎臓のほんの一部しか含まれていません
So it's obvious to tell you
だからあなたに言うのは明らかです
We can study this way
私たちはこうやって勉強できる
Otherwise they're going to slice
さもなければ彼らはスライスするだろう
After you cut each slice you're going to slice
各スライスをカットした後、スライスします
look how much it has in it
どれだけ入っているか見てください
this thing is troublesome
これは面倒だ
It's not easy for you to quantify
数値化するのは簡単ではありません
Now we do it like this
今はこんな感じでやります
this tomography
この断層撮影
They agree that they can calculate and say
彼らは計算して言えることに同意します
what condition am i in
私はどんな状態ですか
what a day it will be
どんな日になるだろう
how did it die
どうやって死んだのか
That is, these glomeruli are
つまり、この糸球体は
dead song by song
歌ごとに死んだ
Still getting bad one by one
それでも一つずつ悪くなっていきます
this is doing this to them
これは彼らにこんなことをしているのです
this is very helpful
これはとても役に立ちます
Another thing we do is look at the nerves
私たちが行うもう一つのことは、神経を観察することです
This is our cooperation with the essence-related characters
エッセンス関連キャラクターとの連携です
We hope that the use of S-light can turn silver
S-light を使用するとシルバーになることを期待しています
or even the nerves in the mouse
あるいはマウスの神経さえも
completely by way of tomography
完全に断層撮影法による
start it all at once with a neuro hospital
神経病院ですべてを一度に始めましょう
to various links
いろいろなリンクへ
Go to these Dendrites all at once and get it done
これらの樹状突起に一度に行って完了してください
This project is what we want to send
私たちが送りたいのはこのプロジェクトです
In fact, the most important skill is not in the technology of S beauty
実は一番大切なスキルはS美の技術ではありません
Just like what we just said
今言ったことと同じように
how do you dye
どうやって染めますか
How about Administrate your developer
開発者を管理してみてはいかがでしょうか
with your calibration
あなたの校正で
This is actually the most difficult
実はこれが一番難しいんです
because we already told you
すでにお伝えしたので
You just have to dye it so we can see it
私たちが見えるように染めればいいだけです
You can see its smallest structure
最小構造がわかります
These little ones are its Dendrite
これらの小さなものはそのデンドライトです
It cannot be seen in an optical microscope.
光学顕微鏡では見ることができません。
OK
OK
I think I've probably said a lot more than that.
おそらくそれ以外にもたくさんのことを言ったと思います。
I'll just stop here
ここでやめておきます
Unless you all are interested in seeing other
皆さんが他のものを見ることに興味がない限り、
Maybe
多分
OK
OK
all that's left to do is watch
あとは見守るだけです
Do you have any questions here?
ここで何か質問はありますか？
Just now I
たった今私は
First of all, thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
まず初めに、先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
The question I want to ask is
私が聞きたい質問は
Just like the hand-held laser device that the teacher used to give a speech today
今日先生がスピーチするときに使った手持ち式レーザー装置のように
You can take a laser light gun with your hand
レーザー光線銃を手で持ち運べる
So the laser light can be from such a large
したがって、レーザー光はこのような大きなものから発せられる可能性があります
What was originally a raw device becomes a handheld device
もともとローデバイスだったものがハンドヘルドデバイスになる
Synchronized X-rays and lasers
同期したX線とレーザー
It currently has no way to become minified
現時点では縮小する方法はありません
And what is the reason for the device that is very effective and usable
この装置が非常に効果的で使いやすい理由は何ですか
Another thing I want to ask is
もう一つ聞きたいのは、
Just now you mentioned three more times
今、あと 3 回言いましたね
The teacher's team has the world's first technology
教師チームは世界初のテクノロジーを持っています
But just now in your slideshow
でも今、あなたのスライドショーで
You also mentioned that these devices are finally used
これらのデバイスが最終的に使用されるようになったとも述べました
It's all like a touch
それはすべてタッチのようなものです
or some commercially available equipment
または市販の機器
what's the reason
どういう理由ですか
Said that other units that can also buy these devices
他のユニットでもこれらのデバイスを購入できると述べました
they can't do these things
彼らにはそんなことはできない
Teacher He can do this
先生彼ならこんなこともできるよ
I think the latter question
後者の質問だと思います
what i say is what you say
私の言うことはあなたの言うことです
That is to say, his optical Lens
つまり、彼の光学レンズは
This fact is
この事実は、
If you say yes, no one else will do it
あなたが「はい」と言えば、誰もそれをしません
only we will do
私たちだけがやります
it's a little stretched
少し伸びています
We can only say that others are too lazy to do it
他の人は怠惰すぎてそれを行うことができないとしか言​​えません
or no one else wants to do
もしくは誰もやりたくない
In fact, I will tell our own students
実際、私自身の生徒たちにも言います。
The biggest reason is
最大の理由は、
we have no one else
私たちには他に誰もいません
others can buy
他の人も買うことができます
but others
でも他の人は
For example, TSMC has similar
たとえば、TSMC にも同様の機能があります。
This Evil Writer
この邪悪な作家
But his job is very fixed
しかし彼の仕事は非常に固定されている
i am a friend
私は友達です
He originally started this company
彼はもともとこの会社を立ち上げた
Just do this S-Wang Shen Wei Jing
これをやってください S-Wang Shen Wei Jing
I tell him
私は彼に言います
you can't compete with us
あなたは私たちと競争することはできません
Why
なぜ
because you are a company
あなたは会社だから
you want to profit
あなたは利益を得たいのですか
i bought something
何かを買った
even if you do the same thing
同じことをするとしても
he wants to count
他要算
So they didn't buy it themselves
つまり彼らは自分で買ったわけではない
Evil Writer
悪の作家
he borrowed this one
彼はこれを借りました
he's in california he borrowed this
彼はカリフォルニアにいます、これを借りました
Use this E-BING RIDER
このE-BING RIDERを使用してください
one thousand dollars an hour
1時間あたり1000ドル
because this is the machine
これが機械だから
When Zhongyuan Industry first bought it,
私たち中原工業が初めて購入したとき
Hundreds of millions soon
もうすぐ何億も
that for us
それは私たちにとって
I just said you know we last year
去年知ってるって言ったばかりだよ
Thousands a year
年間数千件
we use
を使用しております
6 to 7 thousand hours
6～7千時間
So only used in E-BING RIDER
したがって、E-BING RIDER でのみ使用されます
you buy outside
外で買うの
so i say you can't compete
だからあなたは競争できないと言います
Because this is what we are doing research we
これが私たちが研究していることなので、
The thing is here, we don't need to think about it every day
大事なことはここにある、毎日それについて考える必要はない
I use
私が使う
So we are not saying that it takes 6,000 an hour to make this device
したがって、このデバイスを作るのに 1 時間に 6,000 ドルかかると言っているわけではありません。
But we spent a lot of energy from 0 to nothing
その代わりに、私たちは0からゼロになるまで多くのエネルギーを費やしました
to learn
学ぶために
It's all these young people who go in slowly and cover their whole body, and then go slowly to fiddle with it.
ゆっくり入ってきて全身を覆い、ゆっくりとイジり始めるのは若い人たちばかりです。
None of this can be taught
これはどれも教えられない
touch it out so it can be done
タッチアウトして実行できるようにする
so this is
それでこれは
I think this is where you say why we
ここが私たちの理由を言うところだと思います
pretty sure
かなり確実な
no one is doing it now
今は誰もやってない
do like us
私たちを好きにしてください
because when you do
なぜなら、そうするときは
It's easy for the people behind to do it
後ろの人はやりやすいよ
When we first started doing
私たちが最初にやり始めたとき
That is to say, at 100nm
つまり、100nmでは
when i was a graduate student
私が大学院生だったとき
We know this kind of device
私たちはこの種の装置を知っています
We never thought to say that today S1
今日そんなこと言うとは思わなかったS1
Can do 100nm
100nmもできる
I said where is that possible?
どこでそれが可能ですか？と私は言いました。
but why we do it
しかしなぜそれをするのか
Because people have already done it
人々はすでにそれを行っているので、
when people have made
人が作ったとき
it's easy when you're doing
やっているときは簡単です
you know it will work
あなたはそれがうまくいくことを知っています
Then when we make it
それから、それができたら
Our students are interested in
私たちの生徒が興味を持っているのは、
young people are interested
若者たちは興味を持っている
He kept touching and touching
彼は触って触り続けた
I found that the more I did the better, the better I did it
やればやるほど良いことがわかりました
this is
これは
The other one is that you have something to play with you there
もう一つは、そこで一緒に遊べるものがあるということです
so this is
それでこれは
maybe that's kinda
たぶんそれはちょっと
does not match the cost
費用が見合わない
If it were the vice president today, tell me
もし今日の副大統領だったら、教えてください
You see you spend $6 million a year
年間600万ドルを費やしていることがわかります
do this thing
このことをする
As a result, none of them were sold.
結果として、どれも売れませんでした。
then there is no way to do it
それならそれをする方法はありません
and the front is
そして正面は
I think it's because of the intractability of X-ray
レントゲンの難解さのせいだと思う
Even if you have a laser, you usually also have a resonance gun
レーザーを持っていても、通常は共鳴銃も持っています
you need this thing in it
あなたはその中にこれを持っています
I want to oscelate and resonate in it
その中で振動して共鳴したい
This X-ray doesn't have it
このレントゲンにはそれがありません
I'm getting a metal box now
今、金属製の箱を入手しています
It goes out with a swipe
スワイプで消えます
and now it uses shreds, they now use electrons to go
そして今では細断を使用し、電子を使用して移動します
make it some coherence
ある程度の一貫性を持たせる
For example, after my electron comes in
たとえば、私の電子が入ってきた後、
I use a magnetic field to make it go to the module
磁場を使用してモジュールに磁場を送ります
The magnetic field module will slowly lose together
磁場モジュールはゆっくりと一緒に失われていきます
After inputting together, it interacts with electrons
一緒に入力した後、電子と相互作用します
it ends up having some coperance, some coherence
最終的にはある程度の協調性と一貫性が得られる
In the end they all feel that they shine together
最後にはみんな一緒に輝くと感じる
At this time, the light is a bit like a laser.
このときの光はレーザーのような感じです。
That part, this is where they are
その部分、ここが彼らの場所です
Everyone is thinking, what Stanford did in the beginning was a few kilometers
誰もが考えている、スタンフォードが最初にやったのは数キロメートルだった
plus the one shot of free electrons made in Europe
さらにヨーロッパ製の自由電子のワンショット
it's five kilometers
5キロです
The 700 meters that Japan is doing now
今日本がやっている700メートル
Then Switzerland and South Korea may be 200 meters away
その場合、スイスと韓国は200メートル離れている可能性があります
So I was thinking that if it is possible to achieve 100 meters or 50 meters
それで100メートルか50メートルを達成できればと考えていました。
But it's hard to do it this way
でもこのままやるのは難しい
like this
このような
How can TSMC still try to accumulate iron from the CCP?
どうしてTSMCはまだ中国共産党から鉄を集めようとしているのでしょうか？
Which step does Taiwan not understand or do not know how to do?
台湾が理解していない、または行う方法を知らないのはどのステップですか?
Why do you have to buy some trial product material from the CCP?
なぜCCPから試用版の材料を購入しなければならないのですか?
interaction first
最初の対話
I haven't researched this, so I can't just talk about it
私は調べていないので、それについて簡単に話すことはできません
But I think if TSMC's technology is the best in the world
でもTSMCの技術が世界一だと思う
I think Director Yang may know better
ヤン監督はもっとよく知っていると思う
So they went to buy from the CCP, I think it may be the only one
それで彼らは中国共産党から買いに行きました、おそらくそれが唯一のものだと思います
One reason is that it is cheaper
理由の一つは安いからです
yeah i don't think so
はい、私はそうは思いません
OK, of course the Chinese Communist Party has
OK、もちろん中国共産党は
When I often go to the mainland, I find that there are many of them
よく本土に行くと、たくさんいるんです。
For example, the SWET detector I just talked about
たとえば、先ほど話した SWET 検出器
No. 3 they also do
3. 彼らもやります
Infrared detector they also do business
赤外線探知機も扱っています
But you can't tell they're selling
でも、売れているとは言えない
These are military industries
これらは軍事産業です
this they all
これはみんな
But other than this for commercial use
ただしこれ以外は商用利用可
They have nothing better to do than use
彼らは使う以外に何もすることがありません
so they are giving
だから彼らは与えている
I don't think there's anything to worry about
何も心配することはないと思います
they buy our stuff
彼らは私たちのものを買う
I'm afraid it's a lot more than I buy from them.
残念ながら、私が買うよりもはるかに高いと思います。
Teacher Wu just mentioned that
呉先生が先ほどおっしゃいました
The image I want to see the most
一番見たい画像
Lung cancer detection
肺がんの検出
introduce that paragraph
その段落を紹介します
Because the question I want to ask is this Scale in Sale
私が聞きたいのはこのScale in Saleだからです
You can also have XX to see
XXを見てもらうこともできます
Is there a structure in Sale?
セールに構造はありますか?
Thanks
ありがとう
This is actually not a very successful work in mice
これは実際にはマウスではあまり成功した研究ではありません
Because we were talking about comparison at the beginning, in fact, looking at this Lung is very good
最初に比較の話をしましたが、実際、この肺を見ると非常に良いです
You can theorize that we are all pieces of this picture put together
私たちは皆一つになっていると理論化できます
In fact, you can zoom in and see very clearly
実際、ズームインすると非常にはっきりと見ることができます
That mouse is actually alive
あのネズミは実は生きている
You can see because when we put together song by song
曲ごとにまとめてみるとわかります
jump it and move
ジャンプして移動してください
So look at the rib we didn't even get it right
それで、肋骨を見てください、私たちはそれを正しく理解していませんでした
We put it like this on purpose
わざとこのように置いています
But you can see Lung and the T-shirt outside
でも外には肺とTシャツが見えます
its texture
その質感
This is the image of it
これがそのイメージです
The latter structure looks obviously different
後者の構造は明らかに異なります
And while you have a solid this in here
そして、ここにしっかりとしたものがある間、
Words of dense tissue Tumor
高密度組織の言葉 腫瘍
Logically speaking, it should be easy
論理的に言えば、それは簡単なはずです
So there is no processing here
したがって、ここでは処理はありません
that's how we see it
それが私たちの見方です
Show it to the doctor
医師に見せてください
Then you can see it in my Circle
そうすれば、私のサークルで見ることができます
draw it
それを描く
This is a Tumor we entered to make it grow
これは私たちが成長させるために入った腫瘍です
Then you can see like I zoom in white
そうしたら、白を拡大したように見えます
I said you don't know if you can see and see
見えるかどうかは分からないと言いました
Here is a Tumor
ここに腫瘍があります
Then you don't know if you can see and see
そうすると、見えても見えても分からないのです。
Then you can see the very grainy one inside it.
すると、その中に非常に粒子の粗いものが見えます。
It is because the lungs are lung cannons one by one
それは肺が一つ一つ肺砲だからです
Of course it's a lung cannon and we're not here
もちろん、それは肺砲であり、私たちはここにはいません
lung cannon
肺砲
but lung cannon it this
でもこれは肺砲だ
How about it
どうでしょうか
Changed the direction of your light
光の方向を変えた
Come out and make you feel like this swish
出てきて、このスウィッシュな気分にさせてください
that this is its this
これはこれです
So this is about 3mm
これで3mmくらいです
It's still about 2mm for this hall door
このホールのドアはまだ2mmくらいです
But we can also do this
しかし、これもできます
About 0.7mm hall door
約0.7mmホールドア
right here
ここにあります
It's actually pretty easy to see
実はかなり見やすいんです
But this paper we always hope to send this
しかし、この論文は常にこれを送りたいと思っています
We call it radiology
私たちはそれを放射線科と呼んでいます
Just do this method, this, this journal
この方法、これ、この日記だけを実行してください
no one to believe
誰も信じない
None of them talk about 0.7mm
0.7mmについては誰も話していません
Is this small in people
これって人が少ないのかな
But the decimal is still quite large
しかし、小数点はまだかなり大きいです
You can see the decimals are not necessarily
小数点は必ずしも必要ではないことがわかります
you can see in person
直接見ることができます
Then these journal medical journals are made for people
そして、これらの医学ジャーナルは人々のために作られています。
He doesn't care about you doing decimal stuff
彼はあなたが小数のことをすることを気にしません
yes
はい
then this is
それならこれは
We actually put a lot of effort into
私たちは実際に多くの労力を費やしました
make it as possible
できるだけそれをする
you can see like here
ここのように見ることができます
This is caused by the face contract
これは顔の収縮が原因です
its first its edges are clearly visible
最初はエッジがはっきりと見えます
The second is this structure inside
2つ目は内部のこの構造です
It's not the same as the muscle on the outside
外側の筋肉とは違います
So if there is a
それで、ある場合
tissue like meat
肉のような組織
It's actually easy to see
実は見やすいんです
This doesn't need any processing
これは加工の必要がありません
I just said that this is called a natural contract
これを自然契約と呼んでいると言いました
Because the lungs are mostly air
肺はほとんど空気なので
Part of it is a lung cannon like this
一部はこんな感じの肺砲です
and now you have a lump of meat in the middle
真ん中に肉の塊ができました
In fact, it is easy to say
実は言うのは簡単です
easily distinguishable
簡単に区別できる
I can show you
お見せできます
This is normal
これは正常です
you can see this lung
この肺が見えます
see quite clearly
かなりはっきりと見える
This middle is this heart
この真ん中がこの心
This is how we can
これが私たちができる方法です
The problem with applying it to people is that
それを人間に適用する場合の問題点は、
still no face contract
まだ顔契約はしていない
There is no hospital yet
まだ病院はない
Can we get people
人を集められるでしょうか
Bring it to Synchro
株式会社シンクロまでお持ちください。
This Europe has done a lot
このヨーロッパは多くのことを成し遂げた
someone made this
誰かがこれを作りました
with aluminum anti-photography
アルミニウム写真防止機能付き
Then there is this cardiovascular noise
次に、心血管系のノイズが発生します
All these prove that the imaging of synchronous radiation
これらすべては、同期放射のイメージングが可能であることを証明しています。
It's much better than what your hospital did.
あなたの病院でやったことよりずっと良いです。
And not only your quality is better
品質が向上するだけではありません
And the Radiation of that Dose will be relatively low
そして、その線量の放射線は比較的低いでしょう
Even without this comparison
この比較をしなくても
Then it should be better compared to it
だったらそれに比べれば良いはずだ
then i know that means
それならそれが意味することはわかっています
the only reason that says
と言う唯一の理由
why not do it in sync
なぜ同期してやらないのか
that is
あれは
no doctor will
医者はそうはしないだろう
just say ok
ただOKと言ってください
You want to make an aluminum anti-photography
アルミ製の写真防止加工をしたい
Okay, I'll take you to the synchrony
OK、シンクロニーに連れて行きます
we are laughing
私たちは笑っています
Synchro
シンクロ
It looks like a factory inside
中はまるで工場のようです
he was scared to death
彼は死ぬほど怖かった
So many Americans they were in
彼らにはとても多くのアメリカ人がいた
when doing a job like this
このような仕事をしているとき
They have to get a special room
彼らは特別な部屋を手に入れなければなりません
There's going to be classical music in there
そこにはクラシック音楽が流れます
people come in to make you comfortable
あなたを快適にするために人々がやって来ます
can feel
感じることができる
But what they do is a small amount of testing
しかし、彼らが行うのは少量のテストです
just to prove that
それを証明するためだけに
Synchronous auxiliary radiation as long as the light source is good enough
光源が十分に優れている限り、同期補助放射
can definitely do this
これは間違いなくできます
but you get rid of God
でもあなたは神を追い出す
Simultaneous shooting can say think of the way
同時撮影は方法を考えて言うことができます
go to the hospital
病院へ行く
Otherwise, this thing does not have much medical value
そうでなければ、このことには医学的価値はあまりありません
I don't ask for advice
アドバイスなんて求めてないよ
I am a doctor at National Taiwan University
私は国立台湾大学の医師です
I study abroad Hover
ホバー留学します
Now is the era of Nano technology
これからはナノテクノロジーの時代です
everything is nano
すべてはナノです
The actual problem is that
実際の問題は、
which hospital can use this
これを使える病院はどこですか
Is there a Nano Machine now?
ナノマシンって今あるの？
There's none
何もない
now we are doing the same
今、私たちは同じことをしています
My son is a thoracic surgeon
私の息子は胸部外科医です
related factories
関連工場
opened by son
息子が開けた
This morning also opened the way
今朝も道が開けました
that is
あれは
you are good
あなたは良いです
very good idea
idea非常好
Did it actually come out?
本当に出たんですか？
which hospital has it?
どこの病院にありますか？
There's none
何もない
we mean now
つまり今
None of the hospitals are using
どの病院も使っていない
So this is what I say
だからこれが私が言うことです
if you have to wait today
今日待たなければならないなら
but no one is doing it
でも誰もやってない
several important companies
いくつかの重要な企業
G. Phillips Siemens
G. フィリップス シーメンス
They all have a research team to do this
彼らは皆、これを行うための研究チームを持っています
The reason everyone gets stuck
みんながつまづいてしまう理由
The technical bottleneck is the same
技術的なボトルネックは同じ
It means I don't have a good enough light source
十分な光源がないことを意味します
Who can you share with today
今日は誰と共有できますか
we had thought
私たちは思っていた
It is said that someone is selling this small copper cloth radiation
この小さな銅布の放射線を誰かが売っているそうです
We also talked to the hospital
病院にも相談しました
For example, when I was with
たとえば、私が一緒にいたとき、
Talked to this dean on Ma Street
マストリートでこの学部長と話しました
He said that if one or two million dollars
彼は、もし100万ドルか200万ドルなら、と言いました。
not too important to them
彼らにとってはそれほど重要ではない
Because of the hospital
病院のせいで
can be recycled
リサイクルできる
He just sees how many years you pay back
彼はあなたが何年で返済するかを見てるだけです
You just have to make sure he's better
彼が良くなることを確認する必要があるだけです
we are sure of this
私たちはこれを確信しています
then he can be placed in the hospital
そうすれば彼は入院できる
they can operate
彼らは操作できる
Doctors don't treat patients
医者は患者を治療しない
send it elsewhere
他の場所に送ってください
He said I have a healing device today
今日は治癒装置があるって言ってた
I want to do politics
政治的になりたい
to do this pointed therapy
この尖った療法を行うには
Yes there is a place in Taiwan
はい、台湾にも場所があります
or to the United States
または米国へ
Some people sent to the United States for treatment
治療のために米国に送られる人もいる
no problem
大丈夫
I can't do video
動画はできない
That's what we've been doing
それが私たちがやってきたことです
Then these big companies are doing it
それから、これらの大企業はそれをやっています
did not give up
諦めなかった
It means that there is still hope for this thing
これはまだ希望があるということです
Then we mentioned it again recently
それから最近またそれについて話しました
This matter is that the Taiwan government began to support
この件については台湾政府が支援を始めた
That is to say, I hope Taiwan will do digital S-light
つまり台湾もデジタルS-lightをやってほしい
something different
何か違います
then we mentioned this
それから私たちはこれについて言及しました
And now there is also a company
そして今では会社もあります
He bought a Swiss brand called Sweet Straight
彼はスウィートストレートというスイスのブランドを買った
This is the chairman of Beiyi
こちらは北宜の会長です
Li Zhude and the others went to buy it.
李卓徳たちはそれを買いに行きました
they want if they evaluate
彼らが評価するなら欲しい
this thing can do
これはできる
Then this may be what they will
そうすれば、彼らはこうなるかもしれない
Then let's say our problem today is
それでは、今日の問題があるとしましょう。
this dose is too low
この用量は低すぎます
not too high
高すぎない
but I am now this
でも私は今これです
Buy a small one of this Micro Focus Source
この Micro Focus Source の小さいものを購入してください
it's good enough
それは十分です
But its Power is too low
しかしそのパワーは低すぎる
You want us to buy a Micro Focus Source
Micro Focus Source を購入してほしいとのこと
It's not yet
まだ
it may be 0. a few watts
0.数ワットかもしれません
so you have to take a chest photo
だから胸の写真を撮らなければならない
you have to take 30 seconds
30秒かかります
Then there is no resolution
それでは解決策はありません
no resolution required
解決策は必要ありません
Human movement, breathing, and heartbeat are useless
人間の動き、呼吸、心拍は役に立たない
So we're going to take this one
それで、これを取り上げます
strength pulls it back
力がそれを引き戻す
but on the other hand
しかし一方で
because we're going to talk now
今から話すから
If I do joints
関節をやったら
Let's move in
引っ越しましょう
you talk to this woman
あなたはこの女性と話します
just be patient
ただ我慢して
stay a little longer
もう少し滞在してください
it might still be possible
まだ可能かもしれない
That chest can't help
その胸はどうしようもない
because you actually told you not to breathe
あなたが実際に息をしないでと言ったからです
your heartbeat these
あなたの鼓動はこれらを
you will vibrate
あなたは振動します
So this is the only difficulty we know of
これが私たちが知っている唯一の困難です
So there is a lot of development on S3
S3 では多くの開発が行われています
That is to say, this is done by physical people.
つまり、これは肉体的な人間によって行われます。
If this is done today
これが今日行われれば
This will go to the market
これは市場に出ます
any left
少し残っている
may i ask
聞いてもいいですか
What is the difference between the so-called winding design imaging and the board design imaging?
いわゆる巻線設計イメージングと基板設計イメージングの違いは何ですか?
Thanks
ありがとう
OK
OK
Around the imaging tracking device
画像追跡装置周辺
In fact, these two are defraction in English.
実はこの2つは英語ではDefactionです。
with Sketch
スケッチ付き
Actually we are doing H3
実際にH3をやっています
We still don't know exactly
まだ正確にはわかりません
These two images are actually talking about
この 2 つの画像が実際に話しているのは、
if i say i'm talking
私が話していると言ったら
We do image restoration
画像修復を行っております
Actually one thing
実は一つのこと
Because when we're doing imaging
なぜなら、私たちがイメージングを行っているときは、
is the intensity that will emit all the S light
すべての S ライトを放射する強度です
absorb it all
全てを吸収する
I can use a negative
ネガティブも使えるよ
I can use a camera
カメラを使えます
get out
取り出す
But now I say for example
しかし今、私は例えばこう言います
Unfortunately I didn't
残念ながらそうしませんでした
For example, when you hit an object with an S light
たとえば、Sライトを物体に当てたとき
look at the light it emits
それが発する光を見てください
You can't find its connection above
上記の接続が見つかりません
so their progress
それで彼らの進歩
Now these S lights
さて、これらのSライト
they can handle
彼らは対処できる
restore it to the way you were
元の状態に戻します
So this includes
したがって、これには以下が含まれます
Intensity of scattered diffraction and scattered S light
散乱回折と散乱S光の強度
so if you ask
それであなたが尋ねたら
That is to say, what is the difference between this and the direct image?
つまり、直接的なイメージと何が違うのでしょうか？
what we were talking about
私たちが話していたこと
Radiology means
放射線科の手段
I just pass through
ただ通り過ぎるだけ
I'm directly behind the image
私は画像のすぐ後ろにいます
I don't see it diverge
分岐しているようには見えません
Diverge directly
直接分岐する
We may when you are doing this radiology in the hospital
私たちはあなたが病院で放射線科を行っているかもしれません
You also have to use this grid to divert these S-Proong
你還要用 this grid 把這些發散的這個 S-prong
Detaly absorb
細部まで吸収する
Don't make the image blurred
画像をぼかさないでください
You just need to see it straight through it
ただそれをまっすぐに見る必要がある
These two are the main differences
この 2 つが主な違いです
That is almost useless to do with medium
それは媒体ではほとんど役に立たない
Because of this needed this destensity
このためにこの密度が必要だった
The most important use of this is to be able to make about one structure
これの最も重要な用途は、約 1 つの構造を作成できることです。
That is to say, I do nt grow the protein into a crystal today
つまり、今日はタンパク質を結晶に成長させません
I put it in the water capacity and spray it in this light
水量に入れてライトにスプレーします
I solved the protein structure
タンパク質の構造を解きました
But just say modern
でもそれが現代なんです
This is why this world spends so much money
これが世界が多額のお金を使う理由です
Each of this free electronic machine is spent all the light
すべての自由電子と機械光がかかります
They are close to one billion US dollars
10億ドルに近い
The United States spent about 100 million
アメリカは約10億ドルを費やしている
Europe is one billion euro
ヨーロッパは10億ユーロ
One billion euro
10億ユーロ
This costs so much
とても費用がかかりました
The only goal you told them to solve this
あなたは彼らを、彼らの唯一の目標はこれを解決することだと言います
Membrane
膜
this protein this membrane protein
このタンパク質 この膜タンパク質
Because this thing can't be used
これは使えないから
Most membrane proteins cannot be borrowed
ほとんどの膜タンパク質は借用できない
so this thing is very important
したがって、これは非常に重要です
So everyone is willing to spend the money
だから誰もが喜んでお金を使います
But its usefulness will not be
しかし、その有用性は失われます
Otherwise like this strong
そうでなければこのように強い
We can say that we can also go to therapy
セラピーに行くこともできると言えます
let's go in
入りましょう
It is possible to enter this Pulse
このパルスを入力することが可能です
Everything around you is destroyed
あなたの周りのすべてが破壊されます
But this is not for this do this
でもこれはそのためじゃない
OK
OK
Eh
えー
Then I surrounded this picture of mine and you have not told you
それから私はこの私の写真を囲みました、そしてあなたはあなたに言っていませんでした
See how it works from here
ここから仕組みをご覧ください
no it's not
いいえ、ちがいます
This is the normal lung
これが正常な肺です
This is a pig lung cannon
これは豚肺砲です
Inside it is its organ
その中にその器官があります
Then we just because the picture is pretty
じゃあ、写真が綺麗だからってだけで
Back to what I just said
今言ったことに戻ります
because of your lungs
あなたの肺のせいで
because we relax the resolution
解像度を緩めるので
Just wanted to see the resolution of the whole
全体の解像度を見たかっただけです
actually not
実際にはそうではありません
But you can zoom in you at that time if you watch him with our best resolution
しかし、最高の解像度で彼を見れば、その時点であなたをズームインできます
probably like this
おそらくこんな感じ
At this time, you can see the lung cannons accumulated one by one
このとき、肺砲が1つずつ蓄積されているのがわかります
So its actually the solution because the lung cannon has to hit dozens of microns
肺砲は数十ミクロンを攻撃する必要があるため、実際にはこれが解決策になります
So resolution is not an issue
したがって解像度は問題ではありません
This is just for show
これはただの見せ物です
But at this resolution, you can't ask for live
しかし、この解像度では、ライブを要求することはできません
I think Dr. Hu gave us a wonderful and simple explanation today.
今日は胡先生が素晴らしく分かりやすい説明をしてくださったと思います。
So everyone gets something
それで誰もが何かを得る
i think he is tired too
彼も疲れていると思う
everybody look
みんな見て
then we thank him very much today
それでは今日は彼にとても感謝しています
Thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
you
あなた